<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <LastAuthor>Quin Matteson</LastAuthor>
  <LastSaved>2016-11-28T23:36:28Z</LastSaved>
  <Version>16.00</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>13200</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>28800</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>0</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>0</WindowTopY>
  <RefModeR1C1/>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s62">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="LocStuff">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="5" ss:ExpandedRowCount="125" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:Width="131.25"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="812.25"/>
   <Column ss:Width="1342.5"/>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ORIGINAL TEXT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TRANSLATED TEXT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">CHARACTER LIMIT</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485985884</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Encyclopedia of Food Science and Cooking</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">สารานุกรมวิทยาศาสตร์การอาหารและการทำอาหาร</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485985885</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from an entry in the Encyclopedia of Food Science and Cooking, 2033 Edition by Elliot N. Shaw]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transglutaminase (TG or TGase):&lt;/b&gt; A naturally occurring enzyme found in plants, animals, and bacteria. TG is often used to bond protein-containing foods together and in the production of foods such as imitation crab meat and fish balls. Known colloquially by chefs as 'meat glue'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Chef Shaw's Tip: Gluing chicken skin to salmon will actually protect the outside of the salmon from overcooking.&lt;/i&gt;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากสารานุกรมวิทยาศาสตร์การอาหารและการทำอาหาร ฉบับปี 2033 โดย Elliot N. Shaw]<br><br><b>ทรานส์กลูตามิเนส (TG หรือ TGase):</b> เอนไซม์ที่เกิดขึ้นตามธรรมชาติในพืช สัตว์ และแบคทีเรีย TG มักใช้ในการเชื่อมอาหารที่มีโปรตีนเข้าด้วยกัน และในการผลิตอาหาร เช่น เนื้อปูเทียมและลูกชิ้นปลา เป็นที่รู้จักกันในหมู่เชฟว่า &apos;กาวเนื้อ&apos;<br><br><i>เคล็ดลับจากเชฟ Shaw: การติดหนังไก่เข้ากับปลาแซลมอนจะช่วยป้องกันไม่ให้ด้านนอกของปลาแซลมอนสุกเกินไป</i></Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485986121</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Heart of the Wok</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">หัวใจแห่งกระทะ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485986122</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Chapter 5 of Heart of the Wok by P. Sue Do]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cooking with a well-seasoned wok can be a sublime, almost spiritual experience. The many layers of the blackened surface are like stored memories of all the meals that have gone in and out of the carbon steel bowl before - now imparting echoes of their rich flavor to every new meal it is tasked to cook.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ 5 ของ Heart of the Wok โดย P. Sue Do]<br><br>การทำอาหารด้วยกระทะที่ปรุงรสมาอย่างดีอาจเป็นประสบการณ์ที่ยอดเยี่ยมเกือบจะศักดิ์สิทธิ์ ชั้นหลายชั้นของพื้นผิวที่ดำคล้ำนั้นเปรียบเสมือนความทรงจำที่เก็บสะสมของอาหารทุกมื้อที่เคยผ่านเข้าออกในกระทะเหล็กคาร์บอนมาก่อน – บัดนี้ได้ส่งผ่านกลิ่นอายของรสชาติอันเข้มข้นไปยังอาหารทุกมื้อใหม่ที่ได้รับมอบหมายให้ปรุง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485986446</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Engineering Control Systems</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ระบบควบคุมทางวิศวกรรม</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485986447</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from the afterword of Engineering Control Systems, by Sven Shird]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a metaphor here, you know. Typically, the objective of control theory is to monitor the output of a system and compare it with the desired output (the reference signal). The difference between the actual and the desired outputs (the error signal) is applied as feedback to the input of the system, to bring the actual output closer to the reference. Good control systems - and good engineers - learn from the past.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทส่งท้ายของ Engineering Control Systems โดย Sven Shird]<br><br>มันมีนัยยะซ่อนอยู่ตรงนี้ คุณรู้ไหม โดยทั่วไปแล้ว เป้าหมายของทฤษฎีการควบคุมคือการตรวจสอบผลลัพธ์ของระบบและเปรียบเทียบกับผลลัพธ์ที่ต้องการ (สัญญาณอ้างอิง) ความแตกต่างระหว่างผลลัพธ์จริงกับผลลัพธ์ที่ต้องการ (สัญญาณข้อผิดพลาด) จะถูกนำไปใช้เป็นฟีดแบ็กในการป้อนข้อมูลของระบบ เพื่อนำผลลัพธ์จริงเข้าใกล้สัญญาณอ้างอิง ระบบควบคุมที่ดี – และวิศวกรที่ดี – เรียนรู้จากอดีต</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987652</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Speech Synthesis And Natural Language Generation</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">การสังเคราะห์เสียงและการสร้างภาษาธรรมชาติ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987653</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Chapter 3 of Speech Synthesis And Natural Language Generation, by Sebastian Smythe]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voice conversion technology enables synthesis systems to generate speech patterns based on their source or entirely new voices, without the need for exhaustive recordings and pre-processing. The quality of the resulting voice depends on the training data as well as the precision of the conversion function and limitations in processing power.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ 3 ของ Speech Synthesis And Natural Language Generation โดย Sebastian Smythe]<br><br>เทคโนโลยีการแปลงเสียงช่วยให้ระบบสังเคราะห์สามารถสร้างรูปแบบเสียงตามแหล่งที่มาหรือสร้างเสียงใหม่ทั้งหมดได้ โดยไม่จำเป็นต้องมีการบันทึกและประมวลผลล่วงหน้าอย่างละเอียด คุณภาพของเสียงที่ได้ขึ้นอยู่กับข้อมูลการฝึกฝน รวมถึงความแม่นยำของฟังก์ชันการแปลงและข้อจำกัดด้านพลังการประมวลผล</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987692</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hands-On Electronics</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">อิเล็กทรอนิกส์ภาคปฏิบัติ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987693</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from the preface to Hands-On Electronics, by Antoinette Sokol]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By working through a series of practical experiments, this humble manual will introduce you to the fundamentals of modern analog and digital electronics. By the end you will be able to construct any simple circuit. As Thomas Edison once said, &quot;To invent, you need a good imagination and a pile of junk.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากคำนำของ Hands-On Electronics โดย Antoinette Sokol]<br><br>ด้วยการทำงานผ่านชุดการทดลองเชิงปฏิบัติ คู่มือฉบับย่อนี้จะแนะนำคุณให้รู้จักกับพื้นฐานของอิเล็กทรอนิกส์อนาล็อกและดิจิทัลสมัยใหม่ เมื่อจบแล้ว คุณจะสามารถสร้างวงจรพื้นฐานใดก็ได้ ดังที่ Thomas Edison เคยกล่าวไว้ว่า &quot;ในการประดิษฐ์ คุณต้องมีจินตนาการที่ดีและกองขยะ&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987713</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Introduction to Survey of Parapsychological Meta-Analysis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บทนำสู่การสำรวจเมตา-อนาไลซิสทางจิตวิทยา</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987714</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Introduction to Survey of Parapsychological Meta-Analysis by Dr. Dayo Igwe]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, conducting a meta-analysis of over 2000 ganzfeld trials - wherein participants are subjected to mild sensory deprivation in order to test for telepathy - reveals a hit rate of 39%. These results are statistically significant, meaning that the success rate is above what could be explained by chance alone. There is no denying it. Something spooky is going on.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจาก Introduction to Survey of Parapsychological Meta-Analysis โดย Dr. Dayo Igwe]<br><br>ตัวอย่างเช่น การวิเคราะห์เมตา-อนาไลซิสของการทดลอง ganzfeld กว่า 2000 ครั้ง ซึ่งผู้เข้าร่วมจะถูกจำกัดการรับรู้ทางประสาทสัมผัสเล็กน้อยเพื่อทดสอบ Telepathy – เผยให้เห็นอัตราความสำเร็จ 39% ผลลัพธ์เหล่านี้มีความสำคัญทางสถิติ หมายความว่าอัตราความสำเร็จสูงกว่าที่สามารถอธิบายได้ด้วยโอกาสเพียงอย่างเดียว ปฏิเสธไม่ได้เลยว่ามีบางสิ่งที่น่าขนลุกเกิดขึ้น</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987737</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Consciousness: The Fire in the Equations</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">จิตสำนึก: เพลิงในสมการ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987738</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Chapter 1, Consciousness: The Fire in the Equations, by Dr. Stuart Penrose]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nature of consciousness remains deeply mysterious. How can the subjective nature of experience - my inner life - be explained in scientific terms? Does consciousness emerge from complex computations among brain neurons? Or is it a fundamental and irreducible property woven into the fabric of the universe?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ 1, Consciousness: The Fire in the Equations โดย Dr. Stuart Penrose]<br><br>ธรรมชาติของจิตสำนึกยังคงเป็นปริศนาลึกซึ้ง ประสบการณ์ส่วนตัว – ชีวิตภายในของผม – จะอธิบายในเชิงวิทยาศาสตร์ได้อย่างไร? จิตสำนึกเกิดขึ้นจากการคำนวณที่ซับซ้อนระหว่างเซลล์ประสาทในสมองหรือไม่? หรือเป็นคุณสมบัติพื้นฐานและไม่สามารถลดทอนได้ที่ถักทออยู่ในโครงสร้างของจักรวาล?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987795</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Principles of Neuroscience, 10th Edition</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">หลักการประสาทวิทยาศาสตร์ ฉบับที่ 10</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987796</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Principles of Neuroscience, 10th Edition]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...the brain was once considered too &quot;warm, wet, and noisy&quot; for seemingly delicate quantum processes. However, the discovery of quantum coherence in biological processes such as plant photosynthesis, avian navigation, and our own sense of smell, paved the way for the eventual discovery of quantum vibrations inside the microtubules of neurons.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจาก Principles of Neuroscience, ฉบับที่ 10]<br><br>...สมองเคยถูกพิจารณาว่า &quot;อบอุ่น ชื้น และมีเสียงดัง&quot; เกินไปสำหรับกระบวนการควอนตัมที่ดูเหมือนละเอียดอ่อน อย่างไรก็ตาม การค้นพบความเชื่อมโยงทางควอนตัมในกระบวนการทางชีวภาพ เช่น การสังเคราะห์แสงของพืช การนำทางของนก และการรับกลิ่นของเราเอง ได้ปูทางไปสู่การค้นพบการสั่นสะเทือนเชิงควอนตัมภายในไมโครทิวบูลของเซลล์ประสาทในที่สุด</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987917</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Midnight Songs, A Classic Anthology of T'ang Dynasty Verse</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เพลงยามเที่ยงคืน, กวีนิพนธ์คลาสสิกสมัยราชวงศ์ถัง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485987918</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from an anthology of T'ang poetry]&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;On the Stork Tower&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;By Wang Zhihuan&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากกวีนิพนธ์สมัยราชวงศ์ถัง]<br><b>บนหอคอยนกกระสา</b><br><i>โดย หวัง จื้อหวน</i><br></Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485988846</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">An Account of Fermi's Question</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกคำถามของ Fermi</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485988847</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a book on the existence of extraterrestrial intelligence, by Dr. Robert James III]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consider that there are billions of stars in the galaxy like our sun, many of them far older. Some of these stars will have Earth-like planets. Some of these planets may have developed intelligent life. Some intelligent life may develop interstellar travel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a civilization began before ours, it seems possible - even probable - that even at the speed of currently envisioned interstellar travel, they could already have the entire galaxy colonized.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The problem is, we haven't detected any such civilizations. Nor have any contacted us. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือเกี่ยวกับการมีอยู่ของสิ่งมีชีวิตทรงภูมิปัญญานอกโลก โดย Dr. Robert James III]<br><br>ลองพิจารณาว่ามีดาวฤกษ์หลายพันล้านดวงในกาแล็กซีเหมือนดวงอาทิตย์ของเรา หลายดวงมีอายุเก่าแก่กว่ามาก ดาวฤกษ์บางดวงจะมีดาวเคราะห์คล้ายโลก ดาวเคราะห์บางดวงอาจพัฒนาสิ่งมีชีวิตทรงภูมิปัญญา สิ่งมีชีวิตทรงภูมิปัญญาบางชนิดอาจพัฒนาการเดินทางระหว่างดวงดาวได้<br><br>หากอารยธรรมหนึ่งเริ่มต้นขึ้นก่อนเรา ก็ดูเหมือนเป็นไปได้ – หรือแม้กระทั่งน่าจะเป็นไปได้ – ว่าแม้ด้วยความเร็วของการเดินทางระหว่างดวงดาวที่คาดการณ์ไว้ในปัจจุบัน พวกเขาก็อาจจะครอบครองกาแล็กซีทั้งหมดแล้ว<br><br>ปัญหาคือ เรายังไม่พบอารยธรรมดังกล่าว และก็ไม่มีใครติดต่อเรามาเลย<br><br>ทำไม?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485989229</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Noetic Field</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">สนามโนเอติก</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485989230</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from &quot;The Noetic Field&quot; Chapter 1, By Dr. Dayo Igwe] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noetic research, like all bold new ideas, has undergone a predictable pattern in the scientific community. First, skeptics ridicule the idea since it violates conventional wisdom and the Laws of Science. Second, skeptics grudgingly concede the idea might be possible in some circumstances, but the evidence is weak. Third, the idea catches the attention of mainstream researchers and, more importantly, the public. Finally, the same skeptics who once laughed at the idea now claim that they thought of it first.  </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ 1 ของ &quot;The Noetic Field&quot; โดย Dr. Dayo Igwe] <br><br>การวิจัยโนเอติก เช่นเดียวกับแนวคิดใหม่ที่กล้าหาญทั้งหมด ได้ผ่านรูปแบบที่คาดเดาได้ในชุมชนวิทยาศาสตร์ ประการแรก ผู้สงสัยเยาะเย้ยแนวคิดนี้เนื่องจากขัดต่อภูมิปัญญาดั้งเดิมและกฎของวิทยาศาสตร์ ประการที่สอง ผู้สงสัยยอมรับอย่างไม่เต็มใจว่าแนวคิดนี้อาจเป็นไปได้ในบางสถานการณ์ แต่หลักฐานยังอ่อนแอ ประการที่สาม แนวคิดนี้ได้รับความสนใจจากนักวิจัยกระแสหลักและที่สำคัญกว่านั้นคือสาธารณชน สุดท้าย ผู้สงสัยคนเดียวกันที่เคยหัวเราะเยาะแนวคิดนี้ ตอนนี้อ้างว่าพวกเขาคิดได้ก่อน </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485989454</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Method.Sci</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">วิธีการ.Sci</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485989455</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from &quot;Architects of the Neurological Revolution.&quot;] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;What if I told you I could turn you into a mathematician on the level of Einstein in under 10 minutes?&quot;&lt;br&gt;I'd say you're full of it. That's the first thought that crosses my mind, but it withers in the face of Alex Yu's conviction. Despite myself, I'm riveted. He's not bullshitting me. Himself? Maybe. Me? No.&lt;br&gt;Alex leans back in his chair. &quot;Welcome to the age of the Neuromod.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจาก &quot;สถาปนิกแห่งการปฏิวัติระบบประสาท&quot;] <br><br>&quot;ถ้าผมบอกคุณว่าผมสามารถเปลี่ยนคุณให้เป็นนักคณิตศาสตร์ระดับ Einstein ได้ภายในเวลาไม่ถึง 10 นาทีล่ะ?&quot;<br>ผมคงบอกว่าคุณพูดเหลวไหล นั่นคือความคิดแรกที่ผุดขึ้นในใจผม แต่มันก็จางหายไปเมื่อเผชิญหน้ากับความเชื่อมั่นของ Alex Yu แม้จะขัดใจตัวเอง ผมก็ยังถูกตรึงไว้ เขาไม่ได้โกหกผม ตัวเขาเอง? อาจจะ ผม? ไม่<br>Alex เอนหลังพิงเก้าอี้ &quot;ยินดีต้อนรับสู่ยุคของ Neuromod&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485994168</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Program Requirements Document</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เอกสารข้อกำหนดโปรแกรม</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515485994169</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a TranStar work manual]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;6.3.3 - Psychological Risk &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studies show that there is a significant likelihood of behavioral conditions and psychiatric disorders emerging among the population of crew stationed for longer than three months. Impacts of behavioral issues are minimized with appropriate tools for monitoring mood and predicting risk, while including as many earth-like amenities and recreations as possible.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากคู่มือการทำงานของ TranStar]<br><br><b>6.3.3 - ความเสี่ยงทางจิตวิทยา <br><br>การศึกษาแสดงให้เห็นว่ามีความเป็นไปได้สูงที่จะเกิดภาวะทางพฤติกรรมและความผิดปกติทางจิตเวชในหมู่ลูกเรือที่ประจำการนานกว่าสามเดือน ผลกระทบของปัญหาพฤติกรรมจะลดลงด้วยเครื่องมือที่เหมาะสมสำหรับการตรวจสอบอารมณ์และการคาดการณ์ความเสี่ยง ในขณะที่รวมสิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกและกิจกรรมสันทนาการที่คล้ายโลกให้มากที่สุด</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486085256</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fatal Fortress Game Master's Tome, 6th ed.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fatal Fortress Game Master&apos;s Tome, ฉบับที่ 6</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486085257</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from the 6th edition Fatal Fortress Rule Book]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greetings, Game Master!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fatal Fortress is a world deprived of sunlight. As Game Master, you will guide a troop of stalwart adventurers through glittering caves crawling with Ratmen, into battles against horrors that have slept for centuries, and deep into the secret heart of the Fatal Fortress itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike other games, Fatal Fortress has no set character classes, instead encouraging players to play their own way by mixing and matching abilities as they are faced with new challenges. This game also features a dramatic magic system where players create their own spells by drawing and combining runes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each player will need a character record sheet, a miniature to represent their character on the combat map, a full set of polyhedral dice, and a thirst for danger!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือคู่มือ Fatal Fortress ฉบับที่ 6]<br><br>สวัสดี Game Master!<br><br>Fatal Fortress คือโลกที่ปราศจากแสงอาทิตย์ ในฐานะ Game Master คุณจะนำกลุ่มนักผจญภัยผู้กล้าหาญผ่านถ้ำระยิบระยับที่เต็มไปด้วย Ratmen เข้าสู่การต่อสู้กับความน่าสะพรึงกลัวที่หลับใหลมานานหลายศตวรรษ และลึกเข้าไปในใจกลางลับของ Fatal Fortress เอง<br><br>ต่างจากเกมอื่น ๆ Fatal Fortress ไม่มีคลาสตัวละครที่กำหนดไว้ แต่ส่งเสริมให้ผู้เล่นเล่นในแบบของตนเองโดยการผสมผสานความสามารถเมื่อเผชิญกับความท้าทายใหม่ ๆ เกมนี้ยังมีระบบเวทมนตร์ที่น่าทึ่งซึ่งผู้เล่นสร้างคาถาของตนเองโดยการวาดและรวมรูน<br><br>ผู้เล่นแต่ละคนจะต้องมีแผ่นบันทึกตัวละคร หุ่นจำลองเพื่อแสดงตัวละครของตนบนแผนที่การต่อสู้ ลูกเต๋าหลายหน้าครบชุด และความกระหายในอันตราย!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486086242</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Neuromod Application Instructions</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">คำแนะนำการใช้งาน Neuromod</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486086243</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warning: Neuromods should only be administered by certified TranStar technicians under controlled conditions. Subject may experience slight discomfort, swelling, or redness of the eye shortly afterward. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Remove Neuromod from vacuum sealed container. &lt;br&gt;2. Press rubberized eyecup firmly against bony orbit of eye socket. &lt;br&gt;3. Keep eye OPEN. &lt;br&gt;4. Depress orange release trigger AND continue to hold Neuromod against eye for 5 minutes. &lt;br&gt;5. Dispose of used Neuromod in provided biohazard bag.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">คำเตือน: Neuromods ควรได้รับการบริหารโดยช่างเทคนิค TranStar ที่ได้รับการรับรองภายใต้สภาวะควบคุมเท่านั้น ผู้รับอาจรู้สึกไม่สบายเล็กน้อย บวม หรือตาแดงหลังจากนั้นไม่นาน <br><br>1. นำ Neuromod ออกจากภาชนะที่ปิดผนึกสุญญากาศ <br>2. กดที่ครอบตาที่เป็นยางให้แน่นกับกระดูกเบ้าตา <br>3. ลืมตาไว้ <br>4. กดไกปลดล็อกสีส้มค้างไว้ และกด Neuromod ค้างไว้ที่ตาเป็นเวลา 5 นาที <br>5. ทิ้ง Neuromod ที่ใช้แล้วในถุงชีวภาพอันตรายที่จัดเตรียมไว้</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486086277</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Fly</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">แมลงวัน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515486086278</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a book of poems by William Blake]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Fly&lt;br&gt;Thy summer's play,&lt;br&gt;My thoughtless hand&lt;br&gt;Has brush'd away.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Am not I&lt;br&gt;A fly like thee?&lt;br&gt;Or art not thou&lt;br&gt;A man like me?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For I dance&lt;br&gt;And drink &amp; sing;&lt;br&gt;Till some blind hand&lt;br&gt;Shall brush my wing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If thought is life&lt;br&gt;And strength &amp; breath;&lt;br&gt;And the want&lt;br&gt;Of thought is death;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then am I&lt;br&gt;A happy fly,&lt;br&gt;If I live,&lt;br&gt;Or if I die.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือกวีนิพนธ์โดย William Blake]<br><br>แมลงวันน้อย<br>การเล่นในฤดูร้อนของเจ้า<br>มือที่ไร้ความคิดของข้า<br>ได้ปัดป่ายไป<br><br>ข้าไม่ใช่<br>แมลงวันเช่นเจ้าหรือ?<br>หรือเจ้าไม่ใช่<br>มนุษย์เช่นข้า?<br><br>เพราะข้าเต้นรำ<br>และดื่ม & ร้องเพลง;<br>จนกว่ามือที่มองไม่เห็น<br>จะปัดปีกข้าไป<br><br>หากความคิดคือชีวิต<br>และความแข็งแกร่ง & ลมหายใจ;<br>และการขาด<br>ความคิดคือความตาย;<br><br>แล้วข้าก็คือ<br>แมลงวันที่มีความสุข<br>หากข้ามีชีวิต<br>หรือหากข้าตาย</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_6732635291224755174</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Exotic Material Extraction Manual</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">คู่มือการสกัดวัสดุแปลกใหม่</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_6732635291224755175</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a manual detailing procedures in the Extraction Lab]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using the extraction workstation, complete the following steps in listed order while a Volunteer test subject is present in the extraction chamber: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(1) Extract Mimic from containment.&lt;br&gt;(2) Release Mimic into material extraction chamber. &lt;br&gt;(3) When multiplication process is complete, extract exotic material. &lt;br&gt;(4) Process material and collect from dispenser tray. &lt;br&gt;(5) Immediately transport remains to the morgue.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากคู่มือที่อธิบายขั้นตอนในห้องปฏิบัติการสกัด]<br><br>ใช้เวิร์กสเตชันการสกัด ทำตามขั้นตอนต่อไปนี้ตามลำดับที่ระบุในขณะที่มีอาสาสมัครทดลองอยู่ในห้องสกัด: <br><br>(1) สกัด Mimic ออกจากภาชนะกักกัน<br>(2) ปล่อย Mimic เข้าไปในห้องสกัดวัสดุ <br>(3) เมื่อกระบวนการเพิ่มจำนวนเสร็จสิ้น ให้สกัดวัสดุแปลกใหม่ <br>(4) ประมวลผลวัสดุและรวบรวมจากถาดจ่าย <br>(5) ขนส่งซากศพไปยังห้องเก็บศพทันที</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945769433</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Orit</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Orit</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945769434</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[A highlighted excerpt from The Song of Deborah in the sacred texts of Beta Israel]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Judges 5:26&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her hand she put to the tent-peg, and her right hand to the workmen's hammer; and with the hammer she smote Sisera, she smote through his head, yea, she pierced and struck through his temples.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่เน้นจาก The Song of Deborah ในคัมภีร์ศักดิ์สิทธิ์ของ Beta Israel]<br><br><b>ผู้วินิจฉัย 5:26</b><br><br>นางเอามือจับหลักเต็นท์ และมือขวาจับค้อนของช่าง; และด้วยค้อนนางก็ทุบ Sisera นางทุบทะลุศีรษะของเขา ใช่แล้ว นางเจาะและทุบทะลุขมับของเขา</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945769784</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Survivor's Account of &quot;The Evacuation&quot; Day 3</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกของผู้รอดชีวิตจาก &quot;การอพยพ&quot; วันที่ 3</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945769785</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;DAY 3:&lt;/b&gt; We had driven far enough that our fuel ran out. More jets flew over, headed toward the city. One circled back and made several passes over us but did not shoot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That night in the desert we sat by the empty truck and listened to the booming of artillery. Flashes of bombs and lightning covered the horizon. In the morning our city was lost in what appeared to be shimmering heat waves. High overhead there were brilliant flashes of light. Some said it was an atomic bomb, and others said it was God's wrath. Today I know it was just an accident. Scientists that thought they knew everything. But they did not. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were so many people lost that day. So many that I can barely comprehend it. But it was Aleeza that hurt my heart. I know she was just a dog and I am ashamed of my feelings. But she did not make this world we live in. She was mine to protect and I failed.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"><b>วันที่ 3:</b> เราขับรถไปไกลพอจนน้ำมันหมด เครื่องบินเจ็ตบินผ่านไปอีกหลายลำ มุ่งหน้าสู่เมือง ลำหนึ่งบินวนกลับมาและบินผ่านเราหลายครั้งแต่ไม่ได้ยิง<br><br>คืนนั้นในทะเลทราย เรานั่งข้างรถบรรทุกเปล่าและฟังเสียงปืนใหญ่ระเบิด แสงวาบของระเบิดและฟ้าผ่าปกคลุมขอบฟ้า ในตอนเช้า เมืองของเราหายไปในสิ่งที่ดูเหมือนคลื่นความร้อนระยิบระยับ เหนือศีรษะมีแสงวาบเจิดจ้า บางคนบอกว่าเป็นระเบิดปรมาณู และบางคนบอกว่าเป็นพระพิโรธของพระเจ้า วันนี้ผมรู้ว่ามันเป็นแค่อุบัติเหตุ นักวิทยาศาสตร์ที่คิดว่าพวกเขารู้ทุกอย่าง แต่พวกเขาไม่รู้<br><br>มีผู้คนมากมายที่สูญหายไปในวันนั้น มากมายจนผมแทบไม่เข้าใจเลย แต่มันคือ Aleeza ที่ทำให้ผมเจ็บปวด ผมรู้ว่าเธอเป็นแค่สุนัข และผมก็ละอายใจกับความรู้สึกของผม แต่เธอไม่ได้สร้างโลกที่เราอยู่ เธอเป็นของผมที่ต้องปกป้อง และผมก็ล้มเหลว</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945770255</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Good Cop / Good Cop</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ตำรวจดี / ตำรวจดี</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564945770256</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a book on interrogation techniques by Dr. Avalon Bayer]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The typical interrogation suspect portrayed by entertainment media is stubborn, clever or even arrogant, entering into a verbal sparring match with the interrogating officer. While this makes for good drama, it's a poor representation of actual cases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is important to note that the majority of suspects &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to talk. Let them. Provide some prompts, but only to keep the words flowing. Do not attempt to direct them, but just keep them talking. My experience - and case-studies back this - has been that most people will move toward the information you want to know if you just listen to them and reaffirm their assumptions when they need it.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือเกี่ยวกับการสอบสวนโดย Dr. Avalon Bayer]<br><br>ผู้ต้องสงสัยในการสอบสวนทั่วไปที่สื่อบันเทิงนำเสนอ มักจะดื้อรั้น ฉลาด หรือแม้กระทั่งหยิ่งยโส เข้าสู่การโต้เถียงด้วยวาจากับเจ้าหน้าที่สอบสวน แม้ว่าสิ่งนี้จะสร้างละครที่ดี แต่ก็เป็นการนำเสนอที่ไม่ดีของคดีจริง<br><br>สิ่งสำคัญคือต้องสังเกตว่าผู้ต้องสงสัยส่วนใหญ่<i>ต้องการ</i>ที่จะพูด ปล่อยให้พวกเขาพูดไป ให้คำถามกระตุ้นบ้าง แต่เพื่อรักษาให้คำพูดไหลลื่น อย่าพยายามชี้นำพวกเขา แต่แค่ให้พวกเขาพูดต่อไป ประสบการณ์ของผม – และกรณีศึกษาต่าง ๆ ก็สนับสนุนสิ่งนี้ – คือคนส่วนใหญ่จะเคลื่อนไปสู่ข้อมูลที่คุณต้องการรู้ หากคุณเพียงแค่ฟังพวกเขาและยืนยันสมมติฐานของพวกเขาเมื่อพวกเขาต้องการ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_6732635291226918091</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Reactor Emergency Procedures</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ขั้นตอนฉุกเฉินของ Reactor</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_6732635291226918092</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from manual of emergency procedures for the SFR2029-03 SuperForge Reactor]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;10 - 16 - 76 Reboot Initialization: Safety Switches&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Safety control switches for all main utilities must be placed in the OFF position in the following order before initializing reactor shutdown:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; (1) Magnetosphere&lt;br&gt; (2) Substation Power Grid&lt;br&gt; (3) Photovoltaic Rings&lt;br&gt; (4) Gravity&lt;br&gt; (5) Life Support&lt;br&gt; (6) Main Reactor</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากคู่มือขั้นตอนฉุกเฉินสำหรับ SFR2029-03 SuperForge Reactor]<br><br><b>10 - 16 - 76 การเริ่มต้นรีบูต: สวิตช์นิรภัย</b><br><br>สวิตช์ควบคุมความปลอดภัยสำหรับสาธารณูปโภคหลักทั้งหมดจะต้องอยู่ในตำแหน่ง OFF ตามลำดับต่อไปนี้ก่อนที่จะเริ่มต้นการปิด Reactor:<br><br> (1) Magnetosphere<br> (2) Substation Power Grid<br> (3) Photovoltaic Rings<br> (4) Gravity<br> (5) Life Support<br> (6) Main Reactor</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947498605</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Grainger's Memoirs</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกความทรงจำของ Grainger</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947498606</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a journal written by Harley Grainger]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9/27/2034&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I should still be down there playing. My guys needed me, and my shoulder just couldn't deliver. I couldn't deliver. I brought a lot of autographed gloves with me and passed them out like candy at Halloween, but it turns out a lot of these test-tubers don't follow sports at all, much less know about my career, short as it was. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the chances Mr. Yu could set me up with the Neuromods I'd need to put me back in the game? Hell, he could buy a franchise and stock it with the greatest players that ever lived. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If I got a Neuromod would it be me playing? The league would never let modded players in. But how would they know?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกประจำวันของ Harley Grainger]<br><br>27/9/2034<br><br>ผมควรจะยังอยู่ที่นั่นเพื่อเล่นอยู่ ลูกทีมของผมต้องการผม แต่ไหล่ของผมก็ไม่สามารถทำได้ ผมทำไม่ได้ ผมนำถุงมือพร้อมลายเซ็นมาเยอะแยะและแจกจ่ายเหมือนขนมในวันฮาโลวีน แต่ปรากฏว่าพวกนักวิทยาศาสตร์เหล่านี้ส่วนใหญ่ไม่สนใจกีฬาเลย ยิ่งไม่ต้องพูดถึงอาชีพของผมที่สั้นนัก<br><br>มีโอกาสแค่ไหนที่ Mr. Yu จะจัดหา Neuromods ที่ผมต้องการเพื่อกลับไปเล่นเกมได้? ให้ตายสิ เขาสามารถซื้อแฟรนไชส์และเติมเต็มด้วยผู้เล่นที่ยิ่งใหญ่ที่สุดเท่าที่เคยมีมาได้<br><br>ถ้าผมได้ Neuromod มันจะเป็นผมที่เล่นอยู่หรือเปล่า? ลีกจะไม่มีทางยอมให้ผู้เล่นที่ใช้ mod เข้าไปได้ แต่พวกเขาจะรู้ได้อย่างไร?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499632</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Space Elevator</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ลิฟต์อวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499633</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from article, &quot;Stairways to Heaven&quot; by Dr. Angelina M. Allen] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early United States dominance of the first operational space elevator - the White Stork Tower - has allowed them to control almost all orbital activities and commerce.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now the rest of the world is playing catch-up. The World Union of Space Industry (WUSI) has calculated that using the Stork facility to aid in construction of a second space elevator would result in construction costs that are one-quarter of the original.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Understandably, US officials have balked at the idea of helping competitors build a cheaper platform that could give them a competitive advantage. Stork representatives maintain that the sizable investment risks for the original platform justify the protection of this economic space.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the meantime, WUSI has aggressively moved to purchase ideal sites for future space elevators. Essentially space-age squatting.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทความ &quot;บันไดสู่สวรรค์&quot; โดย Dr. Angelina M. Allen] <br><br>การครอบงำของสหรัฐอเมริกาในช่วงแรกของลิฟต์อวกาศที่ใช้งานได้จริงแห่งแรก – White Stork Tower – ทำให้พวกเขาสามารถควบคุมกิจกรรมและพาณิชย์ในวงโคจรเกือบทั้งหมดได้ <br><br>ตอนนี้ส่วนที่เหลือของโลกกำลังตามทัน สหภาพอุตสาหกรรมอวกาศโลก (WUSI) ได้คำนวณว่าการใช้สิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกของ Stork เพื่อช่วยในการสร้างลิฟต์อวกาศแห่งที่สองจะส่งผลให้ต้นทุนการก่อสร้างลดลงเหลือหนึ่งในสี่ของต้นทุนเดิม <br><br>เป็นที่เข้าใจได้ว่า เจ้าหน้าที่สหรัฐฯ ได้ปฏิเสธแนวคิดที่จะช่วยคู่แข่งสร้างแพลตฟอร์มที่ถูกกว่าซึ่งอาจทำให้พวกเขามีความได้เปรียบในการแข่งขัน ตัวแทนของ Stork ยืนยันว่าความเสี่ยงจากการลงทุนจำนวนมากสำหรับแพลตฟอร์มเดิมนั้นสมเหตุสมผลกับการปกป้องพื้นที่เศรษฐกิจนี้ <br><br>ในระหว่างนี้ WUSI ได้ดำเนินการอย่างจริงจังเพื่อซื้อพื้นที่ที่เหมาะสมสำหรับลิฟต์อวกาศในอนาคต โดยพื้นฐานแล้วคือการยึดครองพื้นที่ในยุคอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499640</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rising Stars</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ดาวรุ่ง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499641</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s62"><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from article, &quot;Sizzle Report&quot; by Layla Sky] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Frolca, star of the summer blockbuster &quot;Transgressions&quot; did all of his own death-defying stunts in the film. This eccentric A-lister has played the action star in a dozen films and now, after a long hiatus, has returned in better form than ever.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witness Frolca swinging from a crane in our exclusive teaser clips online! Frolca has been seen cavorting with the stunning Cindy Sinclair. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; More in this edition: &lt;br&gt;10 Celebs That Defy Aging! &lt;br&gt;Vacation in Space! &lt;br&gt;2031 Reel Awards Nominees.  &lt;br&gt;Gary Lee Snubbed? &lt;br&gt;Rising Stars Interviews &quot;Transgressions&quot; Newcomer, Will Richson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทความ &quot;Sizzle Report&quot; โดย Layla Sky] <br><br>Antonio Frolca ดาราจากภาพยนตร์ฟอร์มยักษ์ช่วงฤดูร้อน &quot;Transgressions&quot; ได้แสดงฉากสตันท์ที่ท้าความตายทั้งหมดด้วยตัวเองในภาพยนตร์ ดาราเอลิสต์ผู้แปลกประหลาดคนนี้เคยรับบทเป็นดาราแอคชั่นในภาพยนตร์หลายสิบเรื่อง และตอนนี้ หลังจากหยุดพักไปนาน เขาก็กลับมาในฟอร์มที่ดีกว่าเดิม <br><br>ชม Frolca แกว่งตัวจากเครนในคลิปทีเซอร์สุดพิเศษของเราทางออนไลน์! Frolca ถูกพบเห็นว่ากำลังสนุกสนานกับ Cindy Sinclair ผู้สวยงาม <br><br> เพิ่มเติมในฉบับนี้: <br>10 ดาราที่ท้าทายความชรา! <br>พักผ่อนในอวกาศ! <br>ผู้ได้รับการเสนอชื่อเข้าชิงรางวัล 2031 Reel Awards <br>Gary Lee ถูกเมิน? <br>Rising Stars สัมภาษณ์ Will Richson นักแสดงหน้าใหม่จาก &quot;Transgressions&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499643</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Global Unity Games</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">การแข่งขัน Global Unity Games</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499644</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a gaming magazine article, &quot;Altered Humans&quot; by Halo Michaelson] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Global Unity Games have come to a close, but final medal totals for the participating nations are in limbo amid allegations of neural enhancements and next-generation pharmaceutical use. Every year these games see previous records shattered, and the latest is no exception. By a stunning margin.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทความในนิตยสารเกม &quot;Altered Humans&quot; โดย Halo Michaelson] <br><br>การแข่งขัน Global Unity Games ได้สิ้นสุดลงแล้ว แต่ยอดเหรียญรางวัลสุดท้ายสำหรับประเทศที่เข้าร่วมยังคงไม่แน่นอน ท่ามกลางข้อกล่าวหาเรื่องการเสริมสร้างระบบประสาทและการใช้ยาแห่งอนาคต ทุกปีการแข่งขันเหล่านี้จะเห็นสถิติเดิมถูกทำลาย และครั้งล่าสุดก็ไม่มีข้อยกเว้น ด้วยคะแนนที่น่าทึ่ง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499646</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Terraforming Mars</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">การปรับสภาพดาวอังคาร</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499647</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from an article on the colonization of Mars, by Dan Ousley] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...but the costs of these Mars installations and their continued maintenance is staggering - and their spartan shells are a far cry from the idyllic colonies pictured by turn of the century inspirational space tourism posters.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All that might be about to change. In a rare interview, TranStar president Alex Yu reveals his vision of a Mars where families in short sleeves can picnic in a grassy field, then pick out the point of light that is Earth after the sun sets.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enabling this vision requires terraforming Mars, the most challenging engineering problem the Human race has ever faced. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yu presents an innocuous gray moss to me. An extremophile organism designed specifically for that purpose. Dubbed &lt;i&gt;Takakia Catherine&lt;/i&gt;, the simple looking plant is actually a fantastically efficient organic machine that, given enough centuries, will convert the Martian atmosphere into something that very much resembles our own.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทความเกี่ยวกับการตั้งถิ่นฐานบนดาวอังคาร โดย Dan Ousley] <br><br>...แต่ค่าใช้จ่ายในการติดตั้งและบำรุงรักษาสิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกบนดาวอังคารเหล่านี้สูงมาก – และโครงสร้างที่เรียบง่ายของพวกมันก็ห่างไกลจากอาณานิคมในฝันที่ปรากฏในโปสเตอร์การท่องเที่ยวอวกาศที่สร้างแรงบันดาลใจเมื่อปลายศตวรรษ <br><br>ทั้งหมดนั้นอาจกำลังจะเปลี่ยนไป ในการสัมภาษณ์ที่ไม่บ่อยนัก Alex Yu ประธาน TranStar ได้เปิดเผยวิสัยทัศน์ของเขาเกี่ยวกับดาวอังคารที่ครอบครัวในเสื้อแขนสั้นสามารถปิกนิกในทุ่งหญ้า แล้วมองหาจุดแสงที่เป็นโลกหลังจากพระอาทิตย์ตก <br><br>การทำให้วิสัยทัศน์นี้เป็นจริงต้องอาศัยการปรับสภาพดาวอังคาร ซึ่งเป็นปัญหาทางวิศวกรรมที่ท้าทายที่สุดที่เผ่าพันธุ์มนุษย์เคยเผชิญมา <br><br>Yu นำเสนอตะไคร่น้ำสีเทาที่ไม่เป็นอันตรายให้ผมดู สิ่งมีชีวิตที่ทนทานต่อสภาพแวดล้อมสุดขีดที่ออกแบบมาเพื่อวัตถุประสงค์นั้นโดยเฉพาะ ชื่อว่า <i>Takakia Catherine</i> พืชที่ดูเรียบง่ายนี้แท้จริงแล้วเป็นเครื่องจักรชีวภาพที่มีประสิทธิภาพอย่างน่าอัศจรรย์ ซึ่งหากมีเวลาเพียงพอหลายศตวรรษ จะเปลี่ยนบรรยากาศของดาวอังคารให้กลายเป็นสิ่งที่คล้ายคลึงกับของเรามาก</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499649</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TranStar Life - Employee Profile</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TranStar Life - ประวัติพนักงาน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947499650</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from quarterly employee newsletter, TranStar Life] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this edition of TranStar Life's &quot;Rising Star&quot; segment, we profile Harley Grainger, a member of the Neuromod Sales Team who is currently stationed aboard Talos I! Some of you might recognize Harley's name from his professional baseball days, when he played second base and wore number 66 for the Tornadoes.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harley was assigned to Talos I two years ago and has made the journey into orbit and back over fifty times. Not bad for someone who is afraid of flying!  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;My time playing baseball forced me to deal with that fear,&quot; he said. &quot;Believe it or not, a shuttle flight to Talos I is far easier than a cross country airliner trip.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากจดหมายข่าวพนักงานรายไตรมาส TranStar Life] <br><br>ในฉบับนี้ของส่วน &quot;ดาวรุ่ง&quot; ของ TranStar Life เราจะนำเสนอประวัติของ Harley Grainger สมาชิกทีมขาย Neuromod ซึ่งปัจจุบันประจำการอยู่บน Talos I! บางท่านอาจจำชื่อ Harley ได้จากสมัยที่เขาเป็นนักเบสบอลอาชีพ เมื่อเขาเล่นตำแหน่งเบสสองและสวมเสื้อหมายเลข 66 ให้กับทีม Tornadoes <br><br>Harley ได้รับมอบหมายให้ไป Talos I เมื่อสองปีที่แล้ว และได้เดินทางขึ้นสู่วงโคจรและกลับมาแล้วกว่าห้าสิบครั้ง ไม่เลวเลยสำหรับคนกลัวการบิน! <br><br>&quot;ช่วงเวลาที่ผมเล่นเบสบอลบังคับให้ผมต้องเผชิญหน้ากับความกลัวนั้น&quot; เขากล่าว &quot;เชื่อหรือไม่ว่า การบินด้วยกระสวยไป Talos I นั้นง่ายกว่าการเดินทางด้วยเครื่องบินข้ามประเทศมาก&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721390</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Survivor's Account of &quot;The Evacuation&quot; Day 2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกของผู้รอดชีวิตจาก &quot;การอพยพ&quot; วันที่ 2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721391</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;DAY 2:&lt;/b&gt; I woke up, still in the street. An M35 truck was stopped near me and the driver was yelling at me to get in. There were several people in the back already - four or five soldiers and about a dozen civilians including children. I got in the truck and someone gave me a bottle of water. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I asked what was happening and a solder just shrugged. I told him I had driven the M35 during my service. People in the truck were crying and I looked back. The pink smoke was now mixed with gray and swirled high into the sky. There was so much of it and it seemed to cover the entire city. We kept picking up people until the truck was full. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before we got to the highway we heard shooting. The soldiers climbed down and readied their weapons. The commander told me to drive the truck as far as possible to the west, then they ran toward the shooting.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"><b>วันที่ 2:</b> ผมตื่นขึ้นมา ยังคงอยู่บนถนน รถบรรทุก M35 คันหนึ่งจอดอยู่ใกล้ผม และคนขับกำลังตะโกนให้ผมขึ้นไป มีคนหลายคนอยู่ด้านหลังแล้ว – ทหารสี่หรือห้าคนและพลเรือนประมาณหนึ่งโหลรวมถึงเด็ก ๆ ผมขึ้นรถบรรทุกและมีคนยื่นขวดน้ำให้ผม<br><br>ผมถามว่าเกิดอะไรขึ้น และทหารคนหนึ่งก็แค่ยักไหล่ ผมบอกเขาว่าผมเคยขับ M35 ตอนที่ผมรับราชการ ผู้คนในรถบรรทุกกำลังร้องไห้ และผมมองย้อนกลับไป ควันสีชมพูตอนนี้ผสมกับสีเทาและหมุนวนสูงขึ้นไปบนท้องฟ้า มีควันมากมายจนดูเหมือนปกคลุมทั้งเมือง เรายังคงรับคนขึ้นรถจนรถเต็ม<br><br>ก่อนที่เราจะถึงทางหลวง เราได้ยินเสียงปืน ทหารลงจากรถและเตรียมอาวุธ ผู้บัญชาการบอกให้ผมขับรถไปทางตะวันตกให้ไกลที่สุดเท่าที่จะทำได้ แล้วพวกเขาก็วิ่งไปทางเสียงปืน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721393</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Survivor's Account of &quot;The Evacuation&quot; Day 1</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกของผู้รอดชีวิตจาก &quot;การอพยพ&quot; วันที่ 1</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721394</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;DAY 1:&lt;/b&gt; I had dropped off my dog at the groomer. Her name was Aleeza. It means Joy. I said goodbye and walked a few blocks to get some cafe botz near the park. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some jets flew over, very low, and the sound was so loud it made me jump. I don't know where they were from but they were bristling with bombs and rockets. Everyone was looking up and the sound of the jets was echoing off the buildings but we could not see them anymore. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sky was clear and I could see pink smoke rising from the direction of the stadium. Then the sirens started. I had not heard them since my childhood. Some people stood confused but my instinct told me to run. Run away from the stadium. Run away from Aleeza. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people were running with me, but we didn't know where to go. I saw a policeman directing people into a basement restaurant. I think it was an old bomb shelter. I looked up at the sky again and saw an airliner. It was not military, I am certain. I think it was going to the airport. While I watched, it turned into glitter without a sound. It was just gone. A man near me began to curse. I fell down and hit my head on the street.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"><b>วันที่ 1:</b> ผมพาสุนัขไปส่งที่ร้านเสริมสวย ชื่อของเธอคือ Aleeza หมายถึงความสุข ผมกล่าวลาและเดินไปสองสามช่วงตึกเพื่อซื้อกาแฟบอทซ์ใกล้สวนสาธารณะ<br><br>เครื่องบินเจ็ตบางลำบินผ่านไปต่ำมาก และเสียงดังมากจนทำให้ผมสะดุ้ง ผมไม่รู้ว่าพวกมันมาจากไหน แต่พวกมันเต็มไปด้วยระเบิดและจรวด ทุกคนมองขึ้นไปบนฟ้า และเสียงเครื่องบินเจ็ตสะท้อนจากอาคาร แต่เราไม่เห็นพวกมันอีกต่อไป<br><br>ท้องฟ้าแจ่มใส และผมเห็นควันสีชมพูลอยขึ้นมาจากทิศทางของสนามกีฬา จากนั้นเสียงไซเรนก็เริ่มดังขึ้น ผมไม่เคยได้ยินเสียงพวกมันเลยตั้งแต่เด็ก บางคนยืนงง แต่สัญชาตญาณของผมบอกให้วิ่ง หนีจากสนามกีฬา หนีจาก Aleeza<br><br>บางคนวิ่งไปกับผม แต่เราไม่รู้ว่าจะไปไหน ผมเห็นตำรวจคนหนึ่งกำลังนำผู้คนเข้าไปในร้านอาหารใต้ดิน ผมคิดว่ามันเป็นหลุมหลบภัยเก่า ผมมองขึ้นไปบนฟ้าอีกครั้งและเห็นเครื่องบินโดยสาร มันไม่ใช่เครื่องบินทหาร ผมแน่ใจ ผมคิดว่ามันกำลังจะไปสนามบิน ขณะที่ผมดูอยู่ มันก็กลายเป็นประกายระยิบระยับโดยไม่มีเสียง มันหายไปแล้ว ชายคนหนึ่งใกล้ผมเริ่มสบถ ผมล้มลงและหัวกระแทกพื้นถนน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721841</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Flight Log: Scott Parker</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">บันทึกการบิน: Scott Parker</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721842</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;Flight Log: Flight 071631B Shuttle &quot;Advent&quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prepared by: Scott Parker - Flight Engineer - Talos I. &lt;br&gt;Departure Point: TranStar Seattle Facility &lt;br&gt;Destination: Talos I&lt;br&gt;Captain: Tom Cooper&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earth liftoff was at 0900. Conditions nominal. Pre-check certified. 4 executive passengers. Mail cargo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight was uneventful until 1133 when radar detected an unidentified shuttle approximately thirty degrees off our flight path at 9,000km. Its drift and rotation indicated malfunctioning maneuvering thrusters. There was no answer to radio calls. Captain Cooper ordered a course adjustment to bring us alongside. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we maneuvered to within 60km, a second shuttle appeared on radar in the vicinity of the drifting vessel. Transponders identified it as a military vessel. We received a radio message to resume our original heading immediately. Captain Cooper asked if assistance was required and the order from the military shuttle was repeated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All highly unusual, but then it got really strange. The captain spotted it first. There was a facility out there and it was running absolutely dark. No lights. Radar transparent. We were too far to see any details, but it was big. Cooper snapped into action, punched in a course to Talos and fired the engines. We moved out as quickly as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our passengers were clueless to the entire encounter. Our arrival at Talos went by smoothly and the passengers and cargo were delivered safely. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"><b>บันทึกการบิน: เที่ยวบิน 071631B กระสวย &quot;Advent&quot;</b><br><br>จัดทำโดย: Scott Parker - วิศวกรการบิน - Talos I <br>จุดออกเดินทาง: TranStar Seattle Facility <br>ปลายทาง: Talos I<br>กัปตัน: Tom Cooper<br><br>การปล่อยตัวจากโลกเวลา 0900 สภาพการณ์ปกติ ได้รับการรับรองการตรวจสอบล่วงหน้า ผู้โดยสารระดับบริหาร 4 ท่าน สินค้าทางไปรษณีย์<br><br>เที่ยวบินเป็นไปอย่างราบรื่นจนกระทั่งเวลา 1133 เมื่อเรดาร์ตรวจพบกระสวยที่ไม่ระบุตัวตนประมาณสามสิบองศาจากเส้นทางการบินของเราที่ระยะ 9,000 กม. การลอยและการหมุนของมันบ่งชี้ว่าเครื่องขับเคลื่อนควบคุมการเคลื่อนที่ทำงานผิดปกติ ไม่มีการตอบสนองต่อการเรียกทางวิทยุ กัปตัน Cooper สั่งปรับเส้นทางเพื่อนำเราเข้าใกล้<br><br>ขณะที่เราเคลื่อนที่เข้าใกล้ภายใน 60 กม. กระสวยลำที่สองปรากฏบนเรดาร์ในบริเวณใกล้เคียงกับยานที่ลอยอยู่ เครื่องส่งสัญญาณระบุว่าเป็นยานทหาร เราได้รับข้อความทางวิทยุให้กลับไปสู่เส้นทางเดิมทันที กัปตัน Cooper ถามว่าต้องการความช่วยเหลือหรือไม่ และคำสั่งจากกระสวยทหารก็ถูกย้ำ<br><br>ทั้งหมดนี้ผิดปกติอย่างมาก แต่แล้วมันก็แปลกประหลาดจริง ๆ กัปตันสังเกตเห็นมันก่อน มีสิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกอยู่ที่นั่นและมันมืดสนิท ไม่มีไฟ เรดาร์ไม่สามารถตรวจจับได้ เราอยู่ไกลเกินกว่าจะเห็นรายละเอียดใด ๆ แต่มันใหญ่มาก Cooper รีบดำเนินการ กำหนดเส้นทางไปยัง Talos และจุดเครื่องยนต์ เราเคลื่อนที่ออกไปอย่างรวดเร็วที่สุด<br><br>ผู้โดยสารของเราไม่รู้เรื่องราวทั้งหมด การมาถึง Talos ของเราเป็นไปอย่างราบรื่น และผู้โดยสารและสินค้าก็ถูกส่งมอบอย่างปลอดภัย </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721851</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pioneers of Space Industry</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ผู้บุกเบิกอุตสาหกรรมอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947721852</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Chapter 11 of Pioneers of Space Industry, by Thaylen Cross]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working aboard a space station like Talos is comparable to working on Earth. Employees tend to forget that they are in space and adapt very well.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By contrast, a trove of psychological and behavioral data has been compiled by a decade-long study of Pytheas employees. The Pytheas facility sits deep in a crater on the Lunar pole, permanently shadowed and surrounded by kilometers of ice. Beneath Pytheas is a vast network of cramped tunnels where helium-3, hydrogen and platinum are mined.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a dark, cold, and often terrifying workplace, cut off from the warm glow of Earth, which extracts a heavy and often fatal toll on the crew.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ 11 ของ Pioneers of Space Industry โดย Thaylen Cross]<br><br>การทำงานบนสถานีอวกาศอย่าง Talos นั้นเทียบเท่ากับการทำงานบนโลก พนักงานมักจะลืมไปว่าพวกเขาอยู่ในอวกาศและปรับตัวได้ดีมาก <br><br>ในทางตรงกันข้าม ข้อมูลทางจิตวิทยาและพฤติกรรมจำนวนมากได้ถูกรวบรวมจากการศึกษาพนักงาน Pytheas เป็นเวลาสิบปี สิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกของ Pytheas ตั้งอยู่ลึกเข้าไปในปล่องภูเขาไฟที่ขั้วดวงจันทร์ ถูกปกคลุมด้วยเงาถาวรและล้อมรอบด้วยน้ำแข็งหลายกิโลเมตร ใต้ Pytheas คือเครือข่ายอุโมงค์แคบ ๆ ขนาดใหญ่ที่ใช้ขุดฮีเลียม-3 ไฮโดรเจน และแพลตตินัม<br><br>นี่คือสถานที่ทำงานที่มืดมิด เย็นยะเยือก และมักจะน่าสะพรึงกลัว ถูกตัดขาดจากแสงอันอบอุ่นของโลก ซึ่งส่งผลกระทบอย่างหนักและมักถึงแก่ชีวิตต่อลูกเรือ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729069</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">MAL Championship</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">การแข่งขัน MAL Championship</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729070</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from article &quot;2031 Championship Series&quot; by Nicolette Dossey] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mechanized Athlete League (MAL) 2031 championship series has come to an exciting close in TranStar's Combat Park, Nevada.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Japanese team operating Lightning Kaiju pulled out a stunning victory over the heavily favored Crimson Mace from Norway.&lt;br&gt;Crimson Mace had the match firmly in hand from the start. While lacking in maneuverability, its capacitors absorbed wild amounts of energy from its opponent and used them to power magnetic shields, creating a feedback loop that Kaiju struggled to counter. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solid blows landed at the 2 minute and 3:30 minute mark by Crimson sent the Japanese machine into a tailspin each time.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coverage of the event was briefly interrupted when a surprise electromagnetic pulse by Lightning Kaiju disrupted cameras while also blinding its opponent. Kaiju then finished a helpless Crimson Mace with its signature KillStroke plasma beam.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The finals were viewed in almost 90 million households worldwide, making it the most watched event in MAL history.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทความ &quot;2031 Championship Series&quot; โดย Nicolette Dossey] <br><br>การแข่งขันชิงแชมป์ Mechanized Athlete League (MAL) ปี 2031 ได้ปิดฉากลงอย่างน่าตื่นเต้นที่ Combat Park ของ TranStar ในรัฐเนวาดา <br><br>ทีมญี่ปุ่นที่ควบคุม Lightning Kaiju คว้าชัยชนะอันน่าทึ่งเหนือ Crimson Mace จากนอร์เวย์ ซึ่งเป็นทีมเต็งอย่างมาก<br>Crimson Mace ควบคุมการแข่งขันได้อย่างมั่นคงตั้งแต่เริ่มต้น แม้จะขาดความคล่องตัว แต่ตัวเก็บประจุของมันดูดซับพลังงานจำนวนมากจากคู่ต่อสู้และใช้พลังงานเหล่านั้นเพื่อขับเคลื่อนเกราะแม่เหล็ก สร้างวงจรป้อนกลับที่ Kaiju พยายามต่อต้าน<br><br>การโจมตีที่หนักหน่วงในนาทีที่ 2 และ 3:30 โดย Crimson ทำให้เครื่องจักรญี่ปุ่นหมุนคว้างทุกครั้ง<br><br>การรายงานข่าวของเหตุการณ์ถูกขัดจังหวะชั่วครู่เมื่อคลื่นแม่เหล็กไฟฟ้าที่ไม่คาดคิดจาก Lightning Kaiju รบกวนกล้องและทำให้คู่ต่อสู้ตาบอดด้วย จากนั้น Kaiju ก็จัดการ Crimson Mace ที่หมดหนทางด้วยลำแสงพลาสมา KillStroke อันเป็นเอกลักษณ์ของมัน<br><br>รอบชิงชนะเลิศมีผู้ชมเกือบ 90 ล้านครัวเรือนทั่วโลก ทำให้เป็นเหตุการณ์ที่มีผู้ชมมากที่สุดในประวัติศาสตร์ MAL</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729139</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">International Art: Talos Edition</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ศิลปะนานาชาติ: ฉบับ Talos</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729140</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The TranStar Corporation commissioned several high profile artists to create works exclusively for Talos I, the orbital research and development facility that has brought us the Neuromod and many other technological wonders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Renowned Belgian sculptor Fredrick Smaart sculpted the work &quot;Smoke Signals&quot; which forms the centerpiece of the employee dining hall. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The installation artist simply known as &quot;Jessie&quot; constructed the chain of marbled glass panels which soar gracefully overhead in the Talos I Lobby.&lt;br&gt;And former street artist Patryk O. designed a series of exclusive posters for TranStar featuring impressions of orbit, eclipse and other celestial themes in his signature geometric style. He also developed the Neuromod promotional image featuring the likeness of actor Daisy Prince.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; TranStar President Alex Yu, commented, &quot;Art inspires, fires our creativity, makes us look beyond our present circumstances to what might be possible.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TranStar Corporation ได้ว่าจ้างศิลปินชื่อดังหลายท่านเพื่อสร้างสรรค์ผลงานเฉพาะสำหรับ Talos I ซึ่งเป็นศูนย์วิจัยและพัฒนาในวงโคจรที่นำ Neuromod และสิ่งมหัศจรรย์ทางเทคโนโลยีอื่น ๆ มาสู่เรา<br><br>Fredrick Smaart ประติมากรชาวเบลเยียมผู้มีชื่อเสียง ได้สร้างสรรค์ผลงาน &quot;Smoke Signals&quot; ซึ่งเป็นจุดศูนย์กลางของห้องอาหารพนักงาน <br><br>ศิลปินจัดวางที่รู้จักกันในนาม &quot;Jessie&quot; ได้สร้างสรรค์โซ่แผงกระจกหินอ่อนที่ลอยสง่างามอยู่เหนือศีรษะใน Talos I Lobby<br>และ Patryk O. อดีตศิลปินข้างถนน ได้ออกแบบชุดโปสเตอร์พิเศษสำหรับ TranStar โดยนำเสนอภาพวงโคจร สุริยุปราคา และธีมท้องฟ้าอื่น ๆ ในสไตล์เรขาคณิตอันเป็นเอกลักษณ์ของเขา เขายังได้พัฒนาภาพโปรโมท Neuromod ที่มีภาพเหมือนของนักแสดง Daisy Prince<br><br> Alex Yu ประธาน TranStar แสดงความคิดเห็นว่า &quot;ศิลปะสร้างแรงบันดาลใจ จุดประกายความคิดสร้างสรรค์ของเรา ทำให้เรามองข้ามสถานการณ์ปัจจุบันไปสู่สิ่งที่เป็นไปได้&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729670</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TranStar Uniform Guide</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">คู่มือเครื่องแบบ TranStar</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729671</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from TranStar new hires materials]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Section 11.2.53 TranStar Uniforms&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your TranStar uniform has been designed for your safety, comfort, and to facilitate your work. The uniform must be worn at all times while on board the station. While every effort has been made to make Talos a comfortable and safe place to work, there is always the chance of an accident or hazard. Departmental assignments can be determined by uniform style and color:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(1) Brown &amp; Black - Corporate &amp; Administrative&lt;br&gt;(2) Green &amp; White - Science &amp; Technology&lt;br&gt;(3) Orange - Engineering &amp; Maintenance&lt;br&gt;(4) Blue &amp; Black - Security</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากเอกสารสำหรับพนักงานใหม่ของ TranStar]<br><br><b>ส่วนที่ 11.2.53 เครื่องแบบ TranStar</b><br><br>เครื่องแบบ TranStar ของคุณได้รับการออกแบบมาเพื่อความปลอดภัย ความสะดวกสบาย และเพื่ออำนวยความสะดวกในการทำงานของคุณ ต้องสวมเครื่องแบบตลอดเวลาขณะอยู่บนสถานี แม้ว่าจะมีการพยายามทุกวิถีทางเพื่อให้ Talos เป็นสถานที่ทำงานที่สะดวกสบายและปลอดภัย แต่ก็ยังมีความเป็นไปได้ที่จะเกิดอุบัติเหตุหรืออันตราย การมอบหมายงานของแต่ละแผนกสามารถระบุได้จากรูปแบบและสีของเครื่องแบบ:<br><br>(1) น้ำตาล & ดำ - Corporate & Administrative<br>(2) เขียว & ขาว - Science & Technology<br>(3) ส้ม - Engineering & Maintenance<br>(4) น้ำเงิน & ดำ - Security</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729776</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cooking with Cauliflower</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">การทำอาหารด้วยกะหล่ำดอก</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947729777</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a book on healthy cooking, by Catalina Leigh] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Renowned for its versatility and lush aroma, cauliflower can be substituted in many traditional recipes to boost their nutrient payload without compromising on flavor - faux mashed potatoes, pizza crust, cauli-fried rice pellets and more. But if you're looking to maximize the health benefits of this dimpled delicacy, then steaming is your best bet. Go for the purple variety if you really want to add a blast of color to your plate.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือเกี่ยวกับการทำอาหารเพื่อสุขภาพ โดย Catalina Leigh] <br><br> กะหล่ำดอกเป็นที่รู้จักกันดีในด้านความหลากหลายและกลิ่นหอมชวนรับประทาน สามารถนำมาใช้แทนในสูตรอาหารดั้งเดิมหลายอย่างเพื่อเพิ่มคุณค่าทางโภชนาการโดยไม่ลดทอนรสชาติ – เช่น มันบดเทียม, แป้งพิซซ่า, ข้าวผัดกะหล่ำดอก และอื่น ๆ แต่ถ้าคุณต้องการเพิ่มประโยชน์ต่อสุขภาพของอาหารอันโอชะที่มีรอยบุ๋มนี้ให้สูงสุด การนึ่งคือทางเลือกที่ดีที่สุดของคุณ เลือกพันธุ์สีม่วงหากคุณต้องการเพิ่มสีสันสดใสให้กับจานของคุณ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730187</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis Part III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis ส่วนที่ III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730188</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from lab notes maintained by Rory Manion &amp; Kristine Lloyd]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...may explain how mimics arrived here and how at least one survived in the vacuum inside the Kletka for so long. They can move to an adjacent 'dimensional bubble' where time passes much more slowly, shifting back with the appropriate stimulus (e.g. prey). From the mimic's perspective, a six million year journey to our solar system (in the form of an iron meteor) might only take a few seconds. These things are the ultimate trap door spiders.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกห้องปฏิบัติการที่ดูแลโดย Rory Manion & Kristine Lloyd]<br><br>...อาจอธิบายได้ว่า Mimic มาถึงที่นี่ได้อย่างไร และอย่างน้อยหนึ่งตัวรอดชีวิตในสุญญากาศภายใน Kletka ได้นานเพียงใด พวกมันสามารถเคลื่อนย้ายไปยัง &apos;ฟองมิติ&apos; ที่อยู่ติดกัน ซึ่งเวลาผ่านไปช้าลงมาก โดยจะกลับมาเมื่อมีสิ่งกระตุ้นที่เหมาะสม (เช่น เหยื่อ) จากมุมมองของ Mimic การเดินทางหกล้านปีมายังระบบสุริยะของเรา (ในรูปของอุกกาบาตเหล็ก) อาจใช้เวลาเพียงไม่กี่วินาที สิ่งเหล่านี้คือสุดยอดแมงมุมประตูหลอก</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730190</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis Part II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis ส่วนที่ II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730191</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from lab notes maintained by Rory Manion &amp; Kristine Lloyd]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier models postulated that the Mimic reformed its molecular structure, actually replicating the atomic makeup of target object. We now hypothesize that Mimics are not changing shape at all. When they &quot;mimic&quot; an object, the mimic is no longer objectively present in this universe. The mimic 'swaps' with an object in a parallel reality, but maintains a conscious link (a kind of paradimensional entanglement?) to the object in our universe.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกห้องปฏิบัติการที่ดูแลโดย Rory Manion & Kristine Lloyd]<br><br>แบบจำลองก่อนหน้านี้ตั้งสมมติฐานว่า Mimic ปรับโครงสร้างโมเลกุลของมันใหม่ โดยจำลององค์ประกอบอะตอมของวัตถุเป้าหมายจริง ๆ ตอนนี้เราตั้งสมมติฐานว่า Mimic ไม่ได้เปลี่ยนรูปร่างเลย เมื่อพวกมัน &quot;เลียนแบบ&quot; วัตถุ Mimic จะไม่ปรากฏอยู่ในจักรวาลนี้อีกต่อไป Mimic จะ &apos;สลับ&apos; กับวัตถุในความเป็นจริงคู่ขนาน แต่ยังคงรักษาการเชื่อมโยงทางจิตสำนึก (การพัวพันแบบขนานมิติ?) กับวัตถุในจักรวาลของเรา</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730193</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis Part I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Typhon Mimesis ส่วนที่ I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947730194</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from lab notes maintained by Rory Manion &amp; Kristine Lloyd]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using Mossbauer spectroscopy, we track hyperfine splitting of an isotope embedded in the target object (in this case a standard TranStar coffee mug - the creatures seem to have a weird affinity for them). If the mimic actually altered its atomic structures to duplicate the target object then we would expect the reading to be consistent in the duplicated object. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the alteration occurred, the reading was present, but the frequency had changed. The new object was on a different time scale than the original!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกห้องปฏิบัติการที่ดูแลโดย Rory Manion & Kristine Lloyd]<br><br>การใช้ Mossbauer spectroscopy เราติดตามการแยก hyperfine ของไอโซโทปที่ฝังอยู่ในวัตถุเป้าหมาย (ในกรณีนี้คือแก้วกาแฟ TranStar มาตรฐาน – สิ่งมีชีวิตเหล่านี้ดูเหมือนจะมีความผูกพันแปลก ๆ กับพวกมัน) หาก Mimic เปลี่ยนแปลงโครงสร้างอะตอมเพื่อจำลองวัตถุเป้าหมายจริง ๆ เราก็จะคาดว่าค่าที่อ่านได้จะสอดคล้องกันในวัตถุที่จำลองขึ้นมา<br><br>เมื่อเกิดการเปลี่ยนแปลง ค่าที่อ่านได้ก็ปรากฏขึ้น แต่ความถี่ได้เปลี่ยนไป วัตถุใหม่นั้นอยู่ในช่วงเวลาที่แตกต่างจากต้นฉบับ!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995564</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 1: The Darkstar Anomaly</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 1: ความผิดปกติของ Darkstar</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995565</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s62"><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 1 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Empress Tourmaline gazed past her stern reflection, into the inky black, her angular features circumscribed by the prime viewing dome of the capital ship, Shatterthrax. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Royal Astronomer cleared his throat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Furthermore, your majesty, the Darkstar Anomaly will gain momentum once it begins devouring systems. Within a matter of months the entire galaxy will be consumed. From that point, it will have enough mass to pull other galaxies into its maw.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;I suppose you want me to fund an expedition to find this... Starbender Prism. The way you prattle on about the thing - if it exists - it might be the key to saving our galaxy.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Your majesty...&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;There's only one man I know mad enough to take this on.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;You can't mean...&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Trevor Pulsar.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s62"><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 1 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>จักรพรรดินี Tourmaline จ้องมองผ่านภาพสะท้อนอันเคร่งขรึมของพระองค์ เข้าสู่ความมืดมิดมิดมิดมิด ใบหน้าเหลี่ยมคมของพระองค์ถูกล้อมรอบด้วยโดมชมวิวหลักของยานแม่ Shatterthrax <br><br>นักดาราศาสตร์หลวงกระแอมไอ<br><br>&quot;นอกจากนี้ ฝ่าบาท ความผิดปกติของ Darkstar จะได้รับแรงผลักดันเมื่อมันเริ่มกลืนกินระบบต่าง ๆ ภายในไม่กี่เดือน กาแล็กซีทั้งหมดจะถูกกลืนกิน จากจุดนั้น มันจะมีมวลมากพอที่จะดึงกาแล็กซีอื่น ๆ เข้าสู่ปากของมัน&quot;<br><br>&quot;ข้าคิดว่าเจ้าต้องการให้ข้าสนับสนุนการสำรวจเพื่อค้นหา... Starbender Prism สิ่งที่เจ้าพูดพล่ามถึงมัน – ถ้ามันมีอยู่จริง – มันอาจเป็นกุญแจสำคัญในการกอบกู้กาแล็กซีของเรา&quot;<br><br>&quot;ฝ่าบาท...&quot;<br><br>&quot;มีชายเพียงคนเดียวที่ข้ารู้จักว่าบ้าพอที่จะรับมือกับเรื่องนี้ได้&quot;<br><br>&quot;ฝ่าบาทคงไม่ได้หมายถึง...&quot;<br><br>&quot;Trevor Pulsar&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995648</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 5: Crown of Tumbleweed</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 5: มงกุฎแห่งพืชพุ่ม</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995649</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 5 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Trevor. Get up.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor lifted his head to find the source of the voice. His brain was foggy, and he hadn't heard his old name in what felt like ages. Here, he was Ka'Oli, and the diminutive cliff-dwellers of Dranthor called him king. Rolling out of his royal cot, he allowed his eyes to focus on the figure silhouetted in the doorway to his royal cave.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He knew that uniform. He knew that stance and disapproving glare. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Empress Tourmaline? How did you find me here?&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;The subdermal vacuum-adapteron we had you install came with a beacon. I tracked it here after beating Mercy to death and taking back the Prism. I still need a crack pilot I can trust. Assuming you're through playing royalty with these timid rock-humpers, that is.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor untangled the tumbleweed crown from his matted hair and reflected on his responsibilities to his meek and bethreatened followers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Just one thing before I go.&quot; Trevor picked up his ceremonial Ch'Walla stick and strode out into the light.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 5 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>&quot;Trevor ลุกขึ้น&quot;<br><br>Trevor เงยหน้าขึ้นเพื่อหาแหล่งที่มาของเสียง สมองของเขาพร่ามัว และเขาไม่ได้ยินชื่อเก่าของเขามานานราวกับชั่วกัปชั่วกัลป์ ที่นี่ เขาคือ Ka&apos;Oli และชาวหน้าผาตัวเล็ก ๆ ของ Dranthor เรียกเขาว่ากษัตริย์ เขาพลิกตัวออกจากเตียงหลวง และปล่อยให้ดวงตาของเขาจดจ่อกับร่างที่ปรากฏเป็นเงาในประตูถ้ำหลวงของเขา <br><br>เขารู้จักเครื่องแบบนั้น เขารู้จักท่าทางและการจ้องมองที่ไม่พอใจนั้น <br><br>&quot;จักรพรรดินี Tourmaline? ท่านพบข้าที่นี่ได้อย่างไร?&quot;<br><br>&quot;เครื่องปรับสุญญากาศใต้ผิวหนังที่เราให้เจ้าติดตั้งมาพร้อมกับสัญญาณบอกตำแหน่ง ข้าติดตามมันมาที่นี่หลังจากที่ข้าทุบตี Mercy จนตายและเอา Prism กลับคืนมา ข้ายังคงต้องการนักบินฝีมือดีที่ข้าไว้ใจได้ สมมติว่าเจ้าเลิกเล่นบทบาทกษัตริย์กับพวกชาวหินขี้ขลาดเหล่านี้แล้วนะ&quot;<br><br>Trevor แก้มงกุฎพืชพุ่มออกจากผมที่พันกันของเขา และครุ่นคิดถึงความรับผิดชอบของเขาต่อผู้ติดตามที่อ่อนน้อมและถูกคุกคามของเขา <br><br>&quot;ขออีกอย่างเดียวก่อนที่ข้าจะไป&quot; Trevor หยิบไม้ Ch&apos;Walla พิธีการของเขาขึ้นมาและก้าวออกไปสู่แสงสว่าง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995651</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 4: Backstabbed in the Face</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 4: ถูกแทงข้างหลังเข้าที่หน้า</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995652</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 4 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor's breath fogged up the glass of the airlock door, obscuring the faces of the Royal Astronomer and Mercy, smirking her signature smirk at him from the other side. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Breathe shallow, Pulsar,&quot; the Astronomer menaced, &quot;for these breaths be your last breaths. Now that I have the Prism, the Darkstar Anomaly is under my control and all the galaxy shall...&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Astronomer didn't finish because he was interrupted by his head being exploded by a blast from Mercy's phase pistol, his remaining words replaced by the muted clattering of his teeth against the other side of the airlock door. White breath fog mingled with red mist on the airlock glass, casting Trevor in a pink glow. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Nothing personal, Trevor,&quot; Mercy said. &quot;I'm sure this thing will fetch a nice price on the Thraxian Black Market.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And with that she kicked the airlock button, sending Trevor tumbling out into the unloving black of space.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 4 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>ลมหายใจของ Trevor ทำให้กระจกประตูแอร์ล็อกเป็นฝ้า บดบังใบหน้าของนักดาราศาสตร์หลวงและ Mercy ที่กำลังยิ้มเยาะเขาจากอีกฝั่งหนึ่ง <br><br>&quot;หายใจตื้น ๆ Pulsar&quot; นักดาราศาสตร์ขู่ &quot;เพราะลมหายใจเหล่านี้จะเป็นลมหายใจสุดท้ายของเจ้า ตอนนี้ข้ามี Prism แล้ว ความผิดปกติของ Darkstar ก็อยู่ภายใต้การควบคุมของข้า และกาแล็กซีทั้งหมดจะต้อง...&quot;<br><br>นักดาราศาสตร์ยังพูดไม่จบ เพราะเขาถูกขัดจังหวะด้วยหัวที่ระเบิดจากการยิงของปืนเฟสของ Mercy คำพูดที่เหลือของเขาถูกแทนที่ด้วยเสียงฟันกระทบกันเบา ๆ กับอีกด้านหนึ่งของประตูแอร์ล็อก หมอกควันสีขาวผสมกับหมอกสีแดงบนกระจกแอร์ล็อก ทำให้ Trevor อยู่ในแสงสีชมพู <br><br>&quot;ไม่มีอะไรส่วนตัว Trevor&quot; Mercy กล่าว &quot;ฉันแน่ใจว่าสิ่งนี้จะขายได้ราคาดีในตลาดมืด Thraxian&quot;<br><br>และด้วยคำพูดนั้น เธอก็เตะปุ่มแอร์ล็อก ส่ง Trevor กลิ้งออกไปสู่ความมืดมิดที่ไร้ความรักของอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995654</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 3: Spatial Delivery</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 3: การส่งมอบเชิงพื้นที่</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995655</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 3 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor Pulsar slammed the Talon's engine into overdrive, praying to Z'loar he'd make the gap in the asteroid field before the Mordrax raiders caught up to him. He was on urgent business for Empress Tourmaline, and rotting in a Mordrax kill-prison wouldn't do. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;JT-88!&quot; Trevor barked. &quot;Patch me through to the nearest Royal Fleet outpost.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moments later a scrambled hypersignal could be heard in the cockpit, resolving from static to discordant tones and finally a voice. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Trevor, is that you? This is outpost Lambda. Where in Z'loar's name have you been?&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor replied, cool as a cucumber, &quot;Saving all of your asses. I found the Starbender Prism and I'm coming in hot.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 3 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>Trevor Pulsar เร่งเครื่องยนต์ของ Talon จนสุด กำลังภาวนาต่อ Z&apos;loar ว่าเขาจะผ่านช่องว่างในทุ่งดาวเคราะห์น้อยได้ก่อนที่ผู้บุกรุก Mordrax จะตามทัน เขามีภารกิจเร่งด่วนสำหรับจักรพรรดินี Tourmaline และการเน่าเปื่อยในคุกสังหารของ Mordrax นั้นไม่ดีแน่ <br><br>&quot;JT-88!&quot; Trevor ตะโกน &quot;เชื่อมต่อผมกับด่านหน้าของ Royal Fleet ที่ใกล้ที่สุด&quot;<br><br>ไม่กี่อึดใจต่อมา ก็ได้ยินสัญญาณไฮเปอร์ที่ถูกเข้ารหัสในห้องนักบิน ซึ่งค่อย ๆ เปลี่ยนจากเสียงซ่าเป็นเสียงที่ไม่ลงรอยกัน และในที่สุดก็เป็นเสียง <br><br>&quot;Trevor นั่นคุณหรือเปล่า? นี่คือด่านหน้า Lambda คุณไปอยู่ที่ไหนมากันแน่ในนามของ Z&apos;loar?&quot;<br><br>Trevor ตอบกลับอย่างใจเย็นว่า &quot;ช่วยชีวิตพวกคุณทุกคน ผมเจอ Starbender Prism แล้ว และผมกำลังจะไปถึงแล้ว&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995657</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 2: My Enemy's Enemy's Enemy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 2: ศัตรูของศัตรูของศัตรูของฉัน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995658</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 2 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Mordrax scream-flayer crumpled to the ground in front of her, Mercy flexed her fingers. They ached from all the choking.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor rounded the corner behind her, phase pistol still smoking, the cries of the Mordrax hot on his heels. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercy grunted, &quot;I don't get it Trevor. Why did you spring me from this kill-prison? I've tried to off you, like, seven times.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor replied between blasts of his pistol, &quot;Because you're the only one who's come close to killing me.&quot; Another blast. &quot;And you're the only one I can trust. We're going to steal the Starbender Prism out from under Prince Argon's nose.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercy could only smirk. Her fingers were feeling better already.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 2 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>ขณะที่ Mordrax scream-flayer ล้มลงกองอยู่ตรงหน้าเธอ Mercy ก็ขยับนิ้วของเธอ นิ้วของเธอปวดจากการบีบคอทั้งหมด <br><br>Trevor เลี้ยวโค้งตามหลังเธอ ปืนเฟสของเขายังคงมีควัน เสียงกรีดร้องของ Mordrax ตามติดเขามาอย่างกระชั้นชิด <br><br>Mercy คราง &quot;ฉันไม่เข้าใจ Trevor ทำไมคุณถึงช่วยฉันออกจากคุกสังหารแห่งนี้? ฉันพยายามจะฆ่าคุณมาแล้วประมาณเจ็ดครั้ง&quot;<br><br>Trevor ตอบกลับระหว่างการยิงปืนของเขา &quot;เพราะคุณเป็นคนเดียวที่เกือบจะฆ่าผมได้&quot; ยิงอีกครั้ง &quot;และคุณเป็นคนเดียวที่ผมไว้ใจได้ เราจะขโมย Starbender Prism ออกมาจากใต้จมูกของ Prince Argon&quot;<br><br>Mercy ทำได้เพียงยิ้มเยาะ นิ้วของเธอรู้สึกดีขึ้นแล้ว</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995948</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Starbender Cycle: Book 6: Darkstar Rising</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ชุด Starbender: เล่ม 6: Darkstar กำเนิด</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315995949</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Book 6 of The Starbender Cycle, by Fetcher McMarvin] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three suns of Bel-Kellar were melting into one another in the sky, twisted in their death throes as the Darkstar Anomaly devoured them with disconcerting alacrity. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor had managed to navigate the deadly debris whirling around the Anomaly and crash-land Empress Tourmaline's Royal RaptorCruiser at the base of Mount Mhuul, the synthetic geopyramid which they were now surmounting. They stood panting beside a synthstone altar, its receptacle pulsing with crimson light. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;One minor detail I left out, Trevor,&quot; the empress said between labored breaths. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;We put this into the altar and it devours the anomaly, taking us with it in the process,&quot; Trevor replied, a wink in his grim smile. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;You knew the whole time?&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor wrapped his fingers around hers, both of them now holding the Starbender Prism. &quot;I was born for this,&quot; Trevor replied, and he pushed the prism into the altar.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือชุด Starbender เล่ม 6 โดย Fetcher McMarvin] <br><br>ดวงอาทิตย์ทั้งสามดวงของ Bel-Kellar กำลังหลอมรวมกันบนท้องฟ้า บิดเบี้ยวในการต่อสู้กับความตายขณะที่ Darkstar Anomaly กลืนกินพวกมันด้วยความรวดเร็วที่น่าตกใจ <br><br>Trevor สามารถนำทางผ่านเศษซากอันตรายที่หมุนวนรอบ Anomaly และลงจอดฉุกเฉิน Royal RaptorCruiser ของจักรพรรดินี Tourmaline ที่เชิง Mount Mhuul ซึ่งเป็นพีระมิดธรณีสังเคราะห์ที่พวกเขากำลังปีนขึ้นไป พวกเขายืนหอบอยู่ข้างแท่นบูชาหินสังเคราะห์ ซึ่งช่องรับกำลังเต้นระริกด้วยแสงสีแดงเข้ม <br><br>&quot;มีรายละเอียดเล็กน้อยที่ข้าลืมบอกไป Trevor&quot; จักรพรรดินีกล่าวระหว่างหายใจหอบ <br><br>&quot;เราใส่สิ่งนี้ลงในแท่นบูชา แล้วมันจะกลืนกินความผิดปกติไป พร้อมกับพาเราไปด้วย&quot; Trevor ตอบกลับพร้อมรอยยิ้มเย้ยหยัน <br><br>&quot;คุณรู้มาตลอดเลยเหรอ?&quot;<br><br>Trevor พันนิ้วของเขารอบนิ้วของเธอ ทั้งสองคนตอนนี้กำลังถือ Starbender Prism &quot;ผมเกิดมาเพื่อสิ่งนี้&quot; Trevor ตอบ และเขาก็ผลัก Prism เข้าไปในแท่นบูชา</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404488063</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">After the Space Race</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">หลังจากการแข่งขันอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404488064</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from the Chapter, &quot;The End of the Space Race: The 90s&quot; Dr. Dennis Huld]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...now that space travel was a reality the new challenges became (1) how to recoup beyond &quot;simple&quot; military and science gains and (2) fighting the argument that both groups were ill-equipped to do so. For corporations, the value of space travel was in the acquisition of real estate in what amounted to &quot;international waters,&quot; esp. what laws governed such territorial claims. This allowed for an ethical &quot;loosening of constraints&quot; as well as added security in both containing accidents and the messaging of accidents on space station laboratories.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่ชื่อ &quot;จุดจบของการแข่งขันอวกาศ: ยุค 90&quot; โดย Dr. Dennis Huld]<br><br>...เมื่อการเดินทางในอวกาศกลายเป็นความจริง ความท้าทายใหม่ก็คือ (1) จะฟื้นตัวอย่างไรนอกเหนือจากผลประโยชน์ทางทหารและวิทยาศาสตร์ที่ &quot;เรียบง่าย&quot; และ (2) การต่อสู้กับข้อโต้แย้งที่ว่าทั้งสองกลุ่มไม่มีความพร้อมที่จะทำเช่นนั้น สำหรับบริษัทต่าง ๆ คุณค่าของการเดินทางในอวกาศคือการได้มาซึ่งอสังหาริมทรัพย์ในสิ่งที่เทียบเท่ากับ &quot;น่านน้ำสากล&quot; โดยเฉพาะอย่างยิ่งกฎหมายที่ควบคุมการอ้างสิทธิ์ในดินแดนดังกล่าว สิ่งนี้ทำให้เกิดการ &quot;ผ่อนคลายข้อจำกัด&quot; ทางจริยธรรม รวมถึงความปลอดภัยที่เพิ่มขึ้นทั้งในการควบคุมอุบัติเหตุและการสื่อสารเกี่ยวกับอุบัติเหตุในห้องปฏิบัติการสถานีอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489127</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Neural Horizon I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ขอบฟ้าประสาท I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489128</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[1st Excerpt from &quot;Brandy's Story,&quot; case studies of Neuromod donors and recipients]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...&quot;the process doesn't hurt, not at all.&quot; Brandy Grace speaks happily, enthusiastically. Her smile is radiant, her eyes bright. There is no hint of the Paraplexis eating at her nerve endings. The Olympic medals lie in their glass cases, facing her like an audience. &quot;Yet I still had my love of skating - but the skill felt... trapped inside my head. The mods...&quot; She corrects: &quot;...the Neuromods allowed that skill to be shared with others. A gift.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาครั้งที่ 1 จาก &quot;เรื่องราวของ Brandy&quot; กรณีศึกษาของผู้บริจาคและผู้รับ Neuromod]<br><br>...&quot;กระบวนการนี้ไม่เจ็บเลย ไม่เจ็บเลย&quot; Brandy Grace พูดอย่างมีความสุข กระตือรือร้น รอยยิ้มของเธอเปล่งประกาย ดวงตาของเธอสดใส ไม่มีร่องรอยของ Paraplexis ที่กัดกินปลายประสาทของเธอ เหรียญโอลิมปิกวางอยู่ในตู้กระจก หันหน้าเข้าหาเธอราวกับผู้ชม &quot;แต่ผมก็ยังคงรักการเล่นสเก็ต – แต่ทักษะนั้นรู้สึกเหมือน... ติดอยู่ในหัวของผม The mods...&quot; เธอแก้ไข: &quot;...Neuromods ทำให้ทักษะนั้นสามารถแบ่งปันกับผู้อื่นได้ เป็นของขวัญ&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489314</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Neural Horizon II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ขอบฟ้าประสาท II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489315</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[2nd Excerpt from &quot;Brandy's Story,&quot; case studies of Neuromod donors and recipients]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...I asked Brandy if she felt betrayed by her Paraplexis. She nodded, not in agreement, but understanding my point. &quot;Because they discovered they could map my brain but I can't accept a Neuromod myself?&quot; Her smile became firmer. &quot;I think that makes the gift more meaningful.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be a year before it was (quietly) decided by TranStar to receive no further neural maps - connectomes - from Paraplexis patients, citing unspecified risks.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาครั้งที่ 2 จาก &quot;เรื่องราวของ Brandy&quot; กรณีศึกษาของผู้บริจาคและผู้รับ Neuromod]<br><br>...ผมถาม Brandy ว่าเธอรู้สึกถูกทรยศโดย Paraplexis ของเธอหรือไม่ เธอพยักหน้า ไม่ใช่เพื่อเห็นด้วย แต่เพื่อเข้าใจประเด็นของผม &quot;เพราะพวกเขาค้นพบว่าพวกเขาสามารถทำแผนที่สมองของผมได้ แต่ผมไม่สามารถรับ Neuromod ได้ด้วยตัวเองงั้นหรือ?&quot; รอยยิ้มของเธอมั่นคงขึ้น &quot;ผมคิดว่านั่นทำให้ของขวัญมีความหมายมากขึ้น&quot;<br><br>อีกหนึ่งปีก่อนที่ TranStar จะตัดสินใจ (อย่างเงียบ ๆ) ที่จะไม่รับแผนที่ประสาท – connectomes – จากผู้ป่วย Paraplexis อีกต่อไป โดยอ้างถึงความเสี่ยงที่ไม่ระบุรายละเอียด</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489348</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Neural Horizon III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ขอบฟ้าประสาท III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489349</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Epilogue of &quot;Brandy's Story,&quot; case studies of Neuromod donors and recipients]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I went to visit the Graces. Brandy had passed from her Paraplexis, and the connectome of her ability to skate still remains unused in TranStar databanks. Her parents declined to be interviewed, citing the interviews with Brandy had done more harm than good - rather than raising awareness of the condition, it had shown the division. Brandy had been one of the first to discover her new &quot;handicap.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But if Neuromods are the future, what happens to those unable to use them - or afford them?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[บทส่งท้ายของ &quot;เรื่องราวของ Brandy&quot; กรณีศึกษาของผู้บริจาคและผู้รับ Neuromod]<br><br>ผมไปเยี่ยมครอบครัว Grace Brandy ได้เสียชีวิตลงด้วยโรค Paraplexis ของเธอ และ connectome ของความสามารถในการเล่นสเก็ตของเธอยังคงไม่ได้ถูกใช้ในฐานข้อมูลของ TranStar พ่อแม่ของเธอปฏิเสธที่จะให้สัมภาษณ์ โดยอ้างว่าการสัมภาษณ์กับ Brandy ได้สร้างความเสียหายมากกว่าผลดี – แทนที่จะสร้างความตระหนักรู้เกี่ยวกับอาการนี้ มันกลับแสดงให้เห็นถึงความแตกแยก Brandy เป็นหนึ่งในคนแรก ๆ ที่ค้นพบ &quot;ความพิการ&quot; ใหม่ของเธอ<br><br>แต่ถ้า Neuromods คืออนาคต จะเกิดอะไรขึ้นกับผู้ที่ไม่สามารถใช้มันได้ – หรือไม่มีเงินซื้อ?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489848</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cellular Society</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">สังคมเซลล์</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404489849</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from Cellular Society: The Social Repercussions of Medical Technologies, Dr. Evan Harding]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...yet the effects of medical technology on society's norms can be more pronounced. To cite a &quot;recent&quot; example, one only has to recall cigarette use was often frowned upon as a habit until advances in the food industry that allowed for consumable microspheres that captured and expelled cancer cells from the body. Simultaneously, both the fear of cancer and the stigma attached to smoking vanished within a generation - now smoking is perceived as no more harmful than drinking a soda.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s62"><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจาก Cellular Society: The Social Repercussions of Medical Technologies, Dr. Evan Harding]<br><br>...แต่ผลกระทบของเทคโนโลยีทางการแพทย์ต่อบรรทัดฐานของสังคมอาจเด่นชัดยิ่งขึ้น หากจะยกตัวอย่าง &quot;ล่าสุด&quot; ก็เพียงแค่ต้องนึกถึงการใช้บุหรี่ที่มักถูกมองว่าเป็นนิสัยที่ไม่ดี จนกระทั่งความก้าวหน้าในอุตสาหกรรมอาหารที่อนุญาตให้มีไมโครสเฟียร์ที่บริโภคได้ ซึ่งสามารถจับและขับเซลล์มะเร็งออกจากร่างกายได้ ในเวลาเดียวกัน ทั้งความกลัวมะเร็งและตราบาปที่เกี่ยวข้องกับการสูบบุหรี่ก็หายไปภายในหนึ่งชั่วอายุคน – ตอนนี้การสูบบุหรี่ถูกมองว่าไม่เป็นอันตรายไปกว่าการดื่มน้ำอัดลม</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490197</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Too Far, Too Fast I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เร็วเกินไป ไกลเกินไป I</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490198</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[1st excerpt from Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...in Kennedy's second term, the Space Race reached new heights and without his support may have sputtered completely. A succession of moon launches heralded the coming of an accelerated, energetic space program both within the halls of government and in the public eye. Unusual at the time (esp. in contrast to Kennedy's 1st term), rather than being simply a race between two powers, the Soviets and the United States seemed to be reaching out to space together.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาครั้งที่ 1 จาก Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]<br><br>...ในสมัยที่สองของ Kennedy การแข่งขันอวกาศได้ก้าวไปสู่จุดสูงสุดใหม่ และหากไม่มีการสนับสนุนจากเขา โครงการอาจจะหยุดชะงักไปเลย การปล่อยจรวดสู่ดวงจันทร์ต่อเนื่องกันเป็นการประกาศถึงการมาถึงของโครงการอวกาศที่เร่งรัดและมีพลัง ทั้งในหน่วยงานรัฐบาลและในสายตาของสาธารณชน ซึ่งผิดปกติในเวลานั้น (โดยเฉพาะเมื่อเทียบกับสมัยแรกของ Kennedy) แทนที่จะเป็นการแข่งขันระหว่างสองมหาอำนาจ สหภาพโซเวียตและสหรัฐอเมริกาดูเหมือนจะร่วมมือกันสำรวจอวกาศ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490314</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Too Far, Too Fast II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เร็วเกินไป ไกลเกินไป II</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490315</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[2nd excerpt from Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...and Johnson's term came to an end, paving the way for President Reagan. Even then, the space race was showing signs of faltering, the eager push from previous decades being dulled by the lack of advancement that space had seemed to promise. The Soviet Union had already suffered economic collapse through similar space focus. Many in Washington and the Pentagon found further spending on the space program unpopular, giving rise to a wave of politicians (many of whom had also successfully prevented U.S. involvement in Vietnam) that focused on &quot;solving problems at home.&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาครั้งที่ 2 จาก Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]<br><br>...และวาระของ Johnson ก็สิ้นสุดลง เปิดทางให้ประธานาธิบดี Reagan แม้กระนั้น การแข่งขันอวกาศก็เริ่มแสดงสัญญาณของการชะลอตัว แรงผลักดันอันกระตือรือร้นจากทศวรรษก่อน ๆ ถูกลดทอนลงด้วยการขาดความก้าวหน้าที่อวกาศดูเหมือนจะสัญญาไว้ สหภาพโซเวียตประสบภาวะเศรษฐกิจล่มสลายจากการมุ่งเน้นอวกาศที่คล้ายกัน หลายคนในวอชิงตันและเพนตากอนพบว่าการใช้จ่ายเพิ่มเติมในโครงการอวกาศไม่เป็นที่นิยม ทำให้เกิดคลื่นนักการเมือง (หลายคนประสบความสำเร็จในการป้องกันไม่ให้สหรัฐฯ เข้าไปเกี่ยวข้องกับเวียดนาม) ที่มุ่งเน้นไปที่ &quot;การแก้ปัญหาภายในประเทศ&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490686</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Too Far, Too Fast III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เร็วเกินไป ไกลเกินไป III</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490687</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[3rd excerpt from Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Reagan Era signaled the end of government's strong support for the Space Race. Space now belonged to only the interested few - those who could afford it. Historians argued that had Reagan pushed for a military justification (and with the right marketing), then perhaps the space program might have survived. However, without a significant threat to the U.S., there seemed little incentive. Our only other competitor, the Soviet Union, had already showed the danger of reaching too far, too fast.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาครั้งที่ 3 จาก Commercialization of the Space Program, J.V. Edwards, PhD]<br><br>ยุค Reagan เป็นสัญญาณของการสิ้นสุดการสนับสนุนอย่างแข็งขันของรัฐบาลต่อการแข่งขันอวกาศ อวกาศตอนนี้เป็นของคนเพียงไม่กี่คนที่มีความสนใจ – ผู้ที่สามารถจ่ายได้ นักประวัติศาสตร์โต้แย้งว่าหาก Reagan ผลักดันให้มีเหตุผลทางทหาร (และด้วยการตลาดที่เหมาะสม) โครงการอวกาศอาจจะรอดมาได้ อย่างไรก็ตาม หากไม่มีภัยคุกคามที่สำคัญต่อสหรัฐฯ ก็ดูเหมือนจะไม่มีแรงจูงใจมากนัก คู่แข่งเพียงรายเดียวของเราคือสหภาพโซเวียต ได้แสดงให้เห็นถึงอันตรายของการก้าวไปไกลเกินไป เร็วเกินไปแล้ว</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490904</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">White Noise</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ไวต์นอยส์</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263404490905</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from &quot;White Noise: Perceptions of Imperceptions,&quot; Herndon Rigo]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...more often called &quot;White Noise&quot; due to the telltale spots (said to be like static) in the victim's eyes, &quot;White Noise&quot; isn't just a medical condition. And it's more than the wild, almost witch doctor-like claims of psychic ability (&quot;Doctor&quot; Dayo Igwe, anyone?). It's disenfranchisement. It says the victim can NEVER have a Neuromod, nor can their brain be mapped... it's the end of everything that IS about a person. Who is TranStar to decide? Will we let them add a biological caste system to the human race?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจาก &quot;White Noise: Perceptions of Imperceptions,&quot; Herndon Rigo]<br><br>...มักถูกเรียกว่า &quot;White Noise&quot; เนื่องจากจุดที่บ่งบอก (กล่าวกันว่าเหมือนสัญญาณรบกวน) ในดวงตาของเหยื่อ &quot;White Noise&quot; ไม่ใช่แค่ภาวะทางการแพทย์ และมันเป็นมากกว่าคำกล่าวอ้างที่บ้าคลั่ง เกือบจะเหมือนหมอผีเกี่ยวกับความสามารถทางจิต (ใครก็ได้ &quot;Doctor&quot; Dayo Igwe?) มันคือการตัดสิทธิ์ มันบอกว่าเหยื่อจะไม่มีทางมี Neuromod ได้ และสมองของพวกเขาก็ไม่สามารถทำแผนที่ได้... มันคือจุดจบของทุกสิ่งที่เป็นเกี่ยวกับบุคคล TranStar มีสิทธิ์อะไรที่จะตัดสินใจ? เราจะปล่อยให้พวกเขาเพิ่มระบบวรรณะทางชีวภาพให้กับเผ่าพันธุ์มนุษย์หรือไม่?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417316085698</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">And The West Stood Tall</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">และตะวันตกยังคงยืนหยัด</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417316085699</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from the back cover synopsis of an alternate history novel, by Lance B. Jenkins] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1964, President Kennedy turned his back on American interventionism. But what if America had stood up for its allies in Vietnam? Would Communism still reign in the East? Would the Iron Curtain have fallen? Renowned political commentator Lance B. Jenkins, weaves a gripping alternate account of the days following the Gulf of Tonkin incident and what might have been if America had gone to war in 1964. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Jenkin's historical imagination is meticulous, majestic, poignant. 10/10&quot; - The Liberty Herald</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากเรื่องย่อปกหลังของนวนิยายประวัติศาสตร์ทางเลือก โดย Lance B. Jenkins] <br><br>ในปี 1964 ประธานาธิบดี Kennedy ได้หันหลังให้กับการแทรกแซงของอเมริกา แต่ถ้าอเมริกาได้ยืนหยัดเพื่อพันธมิตรในเวียดนามล่ะ? คอมมิวนิสต์จะยังคงครองอำนาจในตะวันออกหรือไม่? ม่านเหล็กจะล่มสลายหรือไม่? Lance B. Jenkins นักวิจารณ์การเมืองชื่อดัง ได้ร้อยเรียงเรื่องราวทางเลือกที่น่าติดตามของวันหลังจากเหตุการณ์อ่าวตังเกี๋ย และสิ่งที่อาจเกิดขึ้นหากอเมริกาเข้าสู่สงครามในปี 1964 <br><br>&quot;จินตนาการทางประวัติศาสตร์ของ Jenkin นั้นพิถีพิถัน สง่างาม และสะเทือนใจ 10/10&quot; - The Liberty Herald</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405378236</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TranStar Rewards Program</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">โปรแกรมรางวัล TranStar</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405378237</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from TranStar policy handbooks] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Section 8.30.76 Neuromods &amp; Bonuses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At TranStar, we believe in rewarding employees who perform at exemplary levels. Through our Recognition program, employees who are recommended for promotion or commendation are also eligible to receive Neuromods* from the list found in Appendix 4.C.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Please note: these incentives are subject to the limitations outlined in Section 13 and may be revoked or removed at TranStar's discretion, especially in cases involving employee termination, disciplinary action, or emergency protocols.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากคู่มือนโยบายของ TranStar] <br><br><b>ส่วนที่ 8.30.76 Neuromods & โบนัส</b><br><br>ที่ TranStar เราเชื่อในการให้รางวัลแก่พนักงานที่ปฏิบัติงานในระดับที่เป็นแบบอย่าง ผ่านโปรแกรมการยกย่องของเรา พนักงานที่ได้รับการแนะนำให้เลื่อนตำแหน่งหรือได้รับคำชมเชยก็มีสิทธิ์ได้รับ Neuromods* จากรายการที่พบในภาคผนวก 4.C <br><br>*โปรดทราบ: สิ่งจูงใจเหล่านี้อยู่ภายใต้ข้อจำกัดที่ระบุไว้ในส่วนที่ 13 และอาจถูกเพิกถอนหรือยกเลิกได้ตามดุลยพินิจของ TranStar โดยเฉพาะอย่างยิ่งในกรณีที่เกี่ยวข้องกับการเลิกจ้างพนักงาน การดำเนินการทางวินัย หรือระเบียบปฏิบัติฉุกเฉิน</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405391839</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Proxies, Agents, and Personhood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ตัวแทน, ผู้ปฏิบัติการ, และสถานะบุคคล</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405391840</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a book on emulated entities and synthetic intelligence, by Carter Billingsley] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supreme court is set to weigh in on what could be a groundbreaking decision this term: can an Emulated Entity be granted Power of Attorney?  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the last few decades the public has become increasingly familiar with artificial helpers - from the personal assistants on their wrist-watches to the smart home systems that remind you where you put your keys. But more recent advances in hybrotic tech and the genius of connectomics - the ability to map the myriad neuronal connections inside a person's brain - have thrust digital doppelgangers squarely into the legal arena.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently, billionaire Roark Wallace granted Power of Attorney, not to one of his many estranged family members, but to a robotic facsimile of himself named Ransom. Ransom emulates Mr. Wallace's own reasoning, interests, and to some extent personality quirks to the point where the two are nearly indistinguishable - at least over the phone. In person, Ransom's molded ceramic and carbon body - while beautiful - make his true nature unmistakable.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Needless to say, Mr. Wallace's family is not amused, especially concerning Ransom's decision for how to execute Mr. Wallace's will.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากหนังสือเกี่ยวกับเอนทิตีจำลองและปัญญาประดิษฐ์ โดย Carter Billingsley] <br><br>ศาลฎีกากำลังจะพิจารณาตัดสินใจในสิ่งที่อาจเป็นการตัดสินใจครั้งสำคัญในวาระนี้: เอนทิตีจำลองสามารถได้รับอำนาจการมอบฉันทะได้หรือไม่? <br><br>ในช่วงไม่กี่ทศวรรษที่ผ่านมา สาธารณชนเริ่มคุ้นเคยกับผู้ช่วยปัญญาประดิษฐ์มากขึ้นเรื่อย ๆ – ตั้งแต่ผู้ช่วยส่วนตัวบนนาฬิกาข้อมือไปจนถึงระบบสมาร์ทโฮมที่เตือนคุณว่าวางกุญแจไว้ที่ไหน แต่ความก้าวหน้าล่าสุดในเทคโนโลยีไฮบริดและอัจฉริยภาพของ connectomics – ความสามารถในการทำแผนที่การเชื่อมต่อของเซลล์ประสาทจำนวนมากภายในสมองของบุคคล – ได้ผลักดันร่างจำลองดิจิทัลเข้าสู่เวทีทางกฎหมายอย่างเต็มตัว <br><br>เมื่อเร็ว ๆ นี้ มหาเศรษฐี Roark Wallace ได้มอบอำนาจการมอบฉันทะ ไม่ใช่ให้กับสมาชิกในครอบครัวที่ห่างเหินของเขาหลายคน แต่ให้กับหุ่นยนต์จำลองของเขาเองชื่อ Ransom Ransom เลียนแบบการใช้เหตุผล ความสนใจ และในระดับหนึ่ง บุคลิกเฉพาะตัวของ Mr. Wallace จนถึงจุดที่ทั้งสองแทบจะแยกไม่ออก – อย่างน้อยก็ทางโทรศัพท์ เมื่อเจอตัวจริง ร่างกายเซรามิกและคาร์บอนที่หล่อขึ้นรูปของ Ransom – แม้จะสวยงาม – ก็ทำให้ธรรมชาติที่แท้จริงของเขาไม่ผิดเพี้ยน <br><br>ไม่จำเป็นต้องพูด ครอบครัวของ Mr. Wallace ไม่พอใจ โดยเฉพาะอย่างยิ่งเกี่ยวกับการตัดสินใจของ Ransom ในการดำเนินการตามพินัยกรรมของ Mr. Wallace</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405393884</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">I Volunteered</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ผมเป็นอาสาสมัคร</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405393885</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from an interview with a TranStar Volunteer] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;I am not the same man I was two years ago.&quot; Alexei Petrov told me. &quot;Talos I has a way of changing you. Rebuilding you into a better person.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Petrov, along with three other members of the Menshevik movement, were arrested and convicted of the 2029 Red Square attacks which killed 32 people. All four men were sentenced to death. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, just two weeks from his execution, Petrov was approached by tech giant TranStar. The company offered him a second chance. As part of a new program called the TranStar Volunteer Initiative, Petrov was given the opportunity to work as a human test subject in exchange for a commuted sentence. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&quot;They tell me, 'Come up to our space station. Work with us on top secret science projects. Give back to the world from which you have taken so much.' So I did,&quot; Petrov said. &quot;I'm glad I did.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Petrov isn't allowed to talk about the work he did on Talos I, but there's no denying he's a changed man. The former secondary school dropout is now working on doctorate in astrophysics and says he hopes to work for TranStar one day.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากการสัมภาษณ์อาสาสมัคร TranStar] <br><br>&quot;ผมไม่ใช่คนเดิมเมื่อสองปีก่อน&quot; Alexei Petrov บอกผม &quot;Talos I มีวิธีที่จะเปลี่ยนคุณ สร้างคุณใหม่ให้เป็นคนที่ดีขึ้น&quot;<br><br>Petrov พร้อมด้วยสมาชิกอีกสามคนของขบวนการ Menshevik ถูกจับกุมและถูกตัดสินว่ามีความผิดในเหตุการณ์โจมตี Red Square ปี 2029 ซึ่งคร่าชีวิตผู้คน 32 คน ชายทั้งสี่คนถูกตัดสินประหารชีวิต<br><br>อย่างไรก็ตาม เพียงสองสัปดาห์ก่อนการประหารชีวิต Petrov ได้รับการติดต่อจาก TranStar บริษัทเทคโนโลยียักษ์ใหญ่ บริษัทเสนอโอกาสครั้งที่สองให้เขา ในฐานะส่วนหนึ่งของโครงการใหม่ที่เรียกว่า TranStar Volunteer Initiative Petrov ได้รับโอกาสให้ทำงานเป็นอาสาสมัครทดลองมนุษย์เพื่อแลกกับการลดหย่อนโทษ<br><br>&quot;พวกเขาบอกผมว่า &apos;มาที่สถานีอวกาศของเรา ทำงานกับเราในโครงการวิทยาศาสตร์ลับสุดยอด คืนสิ่งดี ๆ ให้กับโลกที่คุณได้เอาไปมากมาย&apos; ผมก็เลยทำ&quot; Petrov กล่าว &quot;ผมดีใจที่ได้ทำ&quot;<br><br>Petrov ไม่ได้รับอนุญาตให้พูดถึงงานที่เขาทำบน Talos I แต่ปฏิเสธไม่ได้ว่าเขาเป็นคนที่เปลี่ยนไป อดีตนักเรียนมัธยมปลายที่เรียนไม่จบกำลังศึกษาปริญญาเอกด้านฟิสิกส์ดาราศาสตร์ และกล่าวว่าเขาหวังว่าจะได้ทำงานให้กับ TranStar สักวันหนึ่ง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405394441</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sales Folder</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">แฟ้มการขาย</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405394442</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a TranStar Sales and Marketing internal memo, by Peter Laney] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don't think we have to worry too much about the side-effects. From what I gathered, it's just a little pinprick near the eye, right? I mean, it looks scary, but I think if we can get advertising to push some of the more appealing pros of NMs, we can shift public attention from that.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm not too worried about the red-eye stuff, either. I don't think any one person in the public sector is gonna manage to get their hands on that many NMs at one time. Not at these prices. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What I find far more worrying, though, are these reports of memory loss during NM removal. I mean, amnesia? Seriously? We can rewire a person's brain, give them any skill we want, but we can't avoid resetting their head back to the moment they got that shit installed if we decide to take it out? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this leaks, it'll kill NM sales. Doesn't matter if you need specialized equipment and training to take one out. No one wants to risk losing years of their life just for the ability to speak French. This can't even go in the fine print. As far as the customer is concerned, NMs are permanent.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกภายในฝ่ายขายและการตลาดของ TranStar โดย Peter Laney] <br><br>ผมไม่คิดว่าเราต้องกังวลมากเกินไปเกี่ยวกับผลข้างเคียง จากที่ผมรวบรวมมา มันก็แค่การเจาะเล็กน้อยใกล้ดวงตาใช่ไหม? คือมันดูน่ากลัวนะ แต่ผมคิดว่าถ้าเราสามารถให้ฝ่ายโฆษณาผลักดันข้อดีที่น่าสนใจของ NMs ได้ เราก็สามารถเปลี่ยนความสนใจของสาธารณชนจากเรื่องนั้นได้ <br><br>ผมไม่ค่อยกังวลเรื่องตาแดงเท่าไหร่ด้วย ผมไม่คิดว่าจะมีใครในภาคสาธารณะที่จะสามารถหา NMs จำนวนมากขนาดนั้นได้ในคราวเดียว ไม่ใช่ในราคานี้ <br><br>แต่สิ่งที่ผมกังวลมากกว่านั้นคือรายงานการสูญเสียความทรงจำระหว่างการถอด NM คือภาวะความจำเสื่อมเหรอ? จริงจังนะ? เราสามารถปรับเปลี่ยนสมองของคนได้ ให้ทักษะอะไรก็ได้ที่เราต้องการ แต่เราไม่สามารถหลีกเลี่ยงการรีเซ็ตสมองของพวกเขากลับไปสู่ช่วงเวลาที่พวกเขาติดตั้งไอ้ของพวกนั้นได้เลยถ้าเราตัดสินใจจะถอดออก?<br><br>ถ้าเรื่องนี้รั่วไหล มันจะฆ่าการขาย NM ไม่สำคัญหรอกว่าคุณต้องใช้อุปกรณ์และการฝึกอบรมพิเศษในการถอดออก ไม่มีใครอยากเสี่ยงที่จะสูญเสียชีวิตไปหลายปีเพียงเพื่อความสามารถในการพูดภาษาฝรั่งเศส เรื่องนี้ไม่สามารถใส่ในตัวอักษรเล็ก ๆ ได้ด้วยซ้ำ สำหรับลูกค้าแล้ว NMs เป็นของถาวร</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405394640</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Behind the Iron Curtain</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">เบื้องหลังม่านเหล็ก</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405394641</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a historical account of the civil unrest within the Soviet Union, by Dr. Luke Manor Banda] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the relationship between the USSR and the United States had warmed in the past few decades, there was little doubt that vestiges of the Iron Curtain still hung icily between the two countries. Indeed, more than a century since its inception, Vladimir Lenin's Communist vision still found itself alive and well within the oft-expanded boundaries of Mother Russia. But with each new Soviet annexation, the USSR began to find that the public outcry no longer came from just the Americans but from amongst its own citizens.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mensheviks, as they came to be known, opposed the aggressive Soviet expansion doctrine. While at first only a minority, the Menshevik movement continued to grow rapidly. Events would ultimately culminate following the Soviet-Indian Intervention with the outbreak of civil unrest led by the Mensheviks and the beginning of the Second Purge.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกประวัติศาสตร์ความไม่สงบภายในสหภาพโซเวียต โดย Dr. Luke Manor Banda] <br><br>แม้ว่าความสัมพันธ์ระหว่างสหภาพโซเวียตและสหรัฐอเมริกาจะอบอุ่นขึ้นในช่วงไม่กี่ทศวรรษที่ผ่านมา แต่ก็ไม่มีข้อสงสัยเลยว่าร่องรอยของม่านเหล็กยังคงแขวนอยู่ระหว่างสองประเทศอย่างเย็นชา อันที่จริง กว่าหนึ่งศตวรรษนับตั้งแต่ก่อตั้ง วิสัยทัศน์คอมมิวนิสต์ของ Vladimir Lenin ยังคงมีชีวิตและดำรงอยู่ได้ดีภายในขอบเขตที่ขยายตัวบ่อยครั้งของ Mother Russia แต่ด้วยการผนวกดินแดนใหม่ของโซเวียตแต่ละครั้ง สหภาพโซเวียตก็เริ่มพบว่าเสียงประท้วงของสาธารณชนไม่ได้มาจากชาวอเมริกันเท่านั้น แต่มาจากพลเมืองของตนเองด้วย <br><br>พวก Mensheviks ซึ่งเป็นที่รู้จักกันในชื่อนี้ ได้ต่อต้านหลักคำสอนการขยายอำนาจของโซเวียตที่ก้าวร้าว แม้ในตอนแรกจะเป็นเพียงชนกลุ่มน้อย แต่ขบวนการ Menshevik ก็ยังคงเติบโตอย่างรวดเร็ว เหตุการณ์ต่าง ๆ จะถึงจุดสูงสุดในที่สุดหลังจากการแทรกแซงของโซเวียต-อินเดีย ด้วยการปะทุของความไม่สงบทางแพ่งที่นำโดย Mensheviks และการเริ่มต้นของการกวาดล้างครั้งที่สอง</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405395592</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Engineering Workbook</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">สมุดงานวิศวกรรม</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263405395593</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from engineer Clive Lawrence's work journal] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Entry 4:&lt;/b&gt; Preliminary tests with an increased spring constant are proving promising, but it's tricky getting fabricators to make them stiff enough but not brittle. Another option is scavenging cargo brought up from earth. Thorstein's assistant has an eagle eye, though. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Entry 4, supplemental:&lt;/b&gt; Dear Clive's diary, he's just trying to impress Mary by coming up with an improvement to her toy gun design. Even if he was smart enough to improve on her work, she'd never give him the time of day. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Entry 4, supplemental supplemental:&lt;/b&gt; I'm well on my way to figuring out how to increase the range and stay the HELL out of my journal Franklin!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบันทึกการทำงานของวิศวกร Clive Lawrence] <br><br><b>บันทึก 4:</b> การทดสอบเบื้องต้นด้วยค่าคงที่สปริงที่เพิ่มขึ้นกำลังให้ผลลัพธ์ที่ดี แต่การทำให้ Fabricator สร้างมันให้แข็งแรงพอแต่ไม่เปราะนั้นเป็นเรื่องยาก อีกทางเลือกหนึ่งคือการเก็บกู้สินค้าที่นำขึ้นมาจากโลก ผู้ช่วยของ Thorstein มีสายตาเฉียบคมมาก <br><br><b>บันทึก 4, เพิ่มเติม:</b> ไดอารี่ของ Clive ที่รัก เขากำลังพยายามสร้างความประทับใจให้ Mary ด้วยการปรับปรุงการออกแบบปืนของเล่นของเธอ แม้ว่าเขาจะฉลาดพอที่จะปรับปรุงงานของเธอ เธอก็จะไม่มีทางสนใจเขาหรอก <br><br><b>บันทึก 4, เพิ่มเติมพิเศษ:</b> ผมกำลังจะหาวิธีเพิ่มระยะและอยู่ให้ห่างจากไดอารี่ของผมซะ Franklin!</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417317220178</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Neuromod Enhanced Yoga: A Beginner's Guide</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">โยคะเสริม Neuromod: คู่มือสำหรับผู้เริ่มต้น</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417317220179</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from pamphlet on neuromod-enhanced Yoga, by Emma Beatty]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yoga is an excellent way for those with the physical series of Neuromod enhancements to grow more in tune with their new capabilities. This is not only enriching, but provides a measure of safety, preventing you from hurting yourself or others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Javelin Asana&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pose is a good starting place for testing your new extended limits, combining strength with balance. The pose begins with a basic handstand and will end with your body completely inverted, all of your weight supported by three fingers on your right hand.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากแผ่นพับเกี่ยวกับโยคะที่เสริมด้วย Neuromod โดย Emma Beatty]<br><br>โยคะเป็นวิธีที่ยอดเยี่ยมสำหรับผู้ที่มีการเสริมสร้าง Neuromod ทางกายภาพ เพื่อให้เข้าถึงความสามารถใหม่ ๆ ของตนเองได้ดียิ่งขึ้น สิ่งนี้ไม่เพียงแต่ช่วยเสริมสร้างเท่านั้น แต่ยังให้ความปลอดภัย ป้องกันไม่ให้คุณทำร้ายตัวเองหรือผู้อื่น<br><br><b>ท่า Javelin Asana</b><br>ท่านี้เป็นจุดเริ่มต้นที่ดีสำหรับการทดสอบขีดจำกัดใหม่ที่ขยายออกไปของคุณ โดยผสมผสานความแข็งแรงเข้ากับความสมดุล ท่านี้เริ่มต้นด้วยการยืนด้วยมือพื้นฐาน และจะจบลงด้วยร่างกายของคุณกลับหัวอย่างสมบูรณ์ โดยน้ำหนักทั้งหมดของคุณรองรับด้วยสามนิ้วบนมือขวาของคุณ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263410469655</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Beyond the Stars, an Unofficial TranStar History</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Beyond the Stars, ประวัติ TranStar อย่างไม่เป็นทางการ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263410469656</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from chapter three of Beyond the Stars, by Samuel Rocher]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed the &quot;Reyes Field Theory,&quot; this discovery proved to be the jumping-off point for a string of scientific miracles TranStar began churning out less than a year later. Take for example the now ubiquitous Operators, which take advatage of a localized levitation effect derived from the theory's gravitational outworkings. Indeed, from the matter-stripping field interactions inside the bowels of Recyclers to the artificial gravity that keeps boots firmly planted on the Italian marble of the Talos I lobby, the impact of Dr. Reyes's theory is undeniable.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[ข้อความที่ตัดตอนมาจากบทที่สามของ Beyond the Stars โดย Samuel Rocher]<br><br>การค้นพบนี้ถูกขนานนามว่า &quot;ทฤษฎีสนาม Reyes&quot; ซึ่งพิสูจน์แล้วว่าเป็นจุดเริ่มต้นของปาฏิหาริย์ทางวิทยาศาสตร์หลายอย่างที่ TranStar เริ่มผลิตออกมาภายในเวลาไม่ถึงหนึ่งปี ตัวอย่างเช่น Operators ที่พบเห็นได้ทั่วไปในปัจจุบัน ซึ่งใช้ประโยชน์จากผลกระทบการลอยตัวเฉพาะที่ที่ได้มาจากผลลัพธ์แรงโน้มถ่วงของทฤษฎีนี้ อันที่จริง ตั้งแต่ปฏิกิริยาสนามที่แยกสสารภายใน Recyclers ไปจนถึงแรงโน้มถ่วงเทียมที่ทำให้รองเท้าติดแน่นอยู่บนหินอ่อนอิตาลีของล็อบบี้ Talos I ผลกระทบของทฤษฎีของ Dr. Reyes นั้นไม่อาจปฏิเสธได้</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <Unsynced/>
   <Selected/>
   <LeftColumnVisible>2</LeftColumnVisible>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
     <ActiveRow>2</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>3</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
 <x:ExcelWorkbook/>
</Workbook>
